{"line": "Konidalasudheer52@gmail.com SUDHEER K +91 7032834577 PROJECT SUMMARY : Education Ananthapuram, India. according to my knowledge. Place: Vizag (K SUDHEER)", "tags": [{"Email": "Konidalasudheer52@gmail.com", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 27, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Konidalasudheer52@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Konidalasudheer52@gmail.com SUDHEER", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 35, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Konidalasudheer52@gmail.com SUDHEER"}, {"Phone": "7032834577", "start_pos": 42, "end_pos": 52, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "7032834577"}, {"GPE": "Ananthapuram, India.", "start_pos": 81, "end_pos": 101, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Ananthapuram, India."}, {"GPE": "Vizag", "start_pos": 136, "end_pos": 141, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Vizag"}, {"PERSON": "(K SUDHEER)", "start_pos": 142, "end_pos": 153, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "(K SUDHEER)"}]}
{"line": "PEDDINTI SAI CHAITANYA SWAROOP S/O Srinivas Rao, E-mail :chaitanya.0747@gmail.com Gunupudi, Bhimavaram, Pin.no : 534201. CAREER OBJECTIVES: Looking for a challenging role in a reputable organization to utilize my technical, database, and management skills for the growth of the organization as well as to enhance my knowledge about new and emerging trends in the sector. To make use of my interpersonal skills to achieve goals of a company that focuses on customer satisfaction and customer experience... ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS:", "tags": [{"Email": "chaitanya.0747@gmail.com", "start_pos": 57, "end_pos": 81, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "chaitanya.0747@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "PEDDINTI SAI CHAITANYA SWAROOP S/O Srinivas Rao,", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 48, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "PEDDINTI SAI CHAITANYA SWAROOP S/O Srinivas Rao,"}, {"Phone": "534201.", "start_pos": 113, "end_pos": 120, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "534201."}]}
{"line": "Joshi Mobile:-9516801977 E-mail:-chandrakantajoshi112@gmail.com", "tags": [{"Email": "-chandrakantajoshi112@gmail.com", "start_pos": 32, "end_pos": 63, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-chandrakantajoshi112@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Joshi", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 5, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Joshi"}]}
{"line": "SONIKA TYAGI Contact - 9354186299, 8650007907 E- mail:sonikatyagi74@gmail.com Current Address - Sector-22,Noida", "tags": [{"Email": "sonikatyagi74@gmail.com", "start_pos": 54, "end_pos": 77, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "sonikatyagi74@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SONIKA TYAGI", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SONIKA TYAGI"}, {"Phone": "9354186299, 8650007907", "start_pos": 23, "end_pos": 45, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9354186299, 8650007907"}]}
{"line": "SHUBHANGI SINGHAL Email :shubhangisinghal007@gmail.com Mob : 8279899602 Linkedin : https://www.linkedin.com/in/Shubhangi-singhal-2922671a1", "tags": [{"Email": "shubhangisinghal007@gmail.com", "start_pos": 25, "end_pos": 54, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "shubhangisinghal007@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SHUBHANGI SINGHAL", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 17, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SHUBHANGI SINGHAL"}, {"Phone": "8279899602", "start_pos": 61, "end_pos": 71, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "8279899602"}]}
{"line": "V.Shanthakumar S/o. N.Venkatesh, D.No.2/30, Bairamangalam (Vill), Bairamangalam (PO), Denkanikottai (Tk), Krishnagiri District, Tamil Nadu. Pin: 635113. Phone:+91-6369313350 OBJECTIVE EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION E-Mail:shanthakumarvenkatesh27@gmail.com To achieve my dream of fulfilling my ambition and goals regarding my career. A challenging career with a team for committed improvement. Institution Er.Perumal Manimekalai College of Engineering, Koneripalli. Board/ SOFT SKILLS   Listening Skills & Communication skill.  Adaptable in any working environment. PERSONAL PROFILE  Willingness to learn new things. Name of Gender Status Languages Known Male Unmarried English & Playing Telugu, English Tamil, & Kannada. Hobbies", "tags": [{"Email": "shanthakumarvenkatesh27@gmail.com", "start_pos": 217, "end_pos": 250, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "shanthakumarvenkatesh27@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "V.Shanthakumar S/o. N.Venkatesh,", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 32, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "V.Shanthakumar S/o. N.Venkatesh,"}, {"EducationDegree": "D.No.2/30,", "start_pos": 33, "end_pos": 43, "tag": "EducationDegree", "type": "EducationDegree", "text": "D.No.2/30,"}, {"GPE": "Tamil Nadu.", "start_pos": 128, "end_pos": 139, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Tamil Nadu."}, {"Phone": "635113.", "start_pos": 145, "end_pos": 152, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "635113."}]}
{"line": "KANCHARLA VAMSHI KRISHNA E-mail:vamshirock007@gmail.com Mobile: +91-8187027033 Personal Profile  Languages Known : English, Telugu and Hindi Name Address Vijaya Colony, Suryapet, :Kancharla Vamshi Krishna Father’s name : Kancharla Yadhagiri Reddy Date of Birth : 27-06-1995 Hobbies : Internet Surfing, Playing Table Tennis and cricket. : c/o K. Yadhagiri Reddy,H.No:1-9-61/24/B, Hyderbad-508213, Telangana. Declaration I hereby declare that the information mentioned above is true to the best of my knowledge. Place: Hyderabad Date: (Vamshi Krishna)", "tags": [{"Email": "vamshirock007@gmail.com", "start_pos": 32, "end_pos": 55, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "vamshirock007@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "KANCHARLA VAMSHI KRISHNA", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 24, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "KANCHARLA VAMSHI KRISHNA"}, {"Phone": "+91-8187027033", "start_pos": 64, "end_pos": 78, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-8187027033"}, {"DOB": "27-06-1995", "start_pos": 262, "end_pos": 272, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "27-06-1995"}, {"PERSON": "Krishna)", "start_pos": 540, "end_pos": 548, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Krishna)"}]}
{"line": "L.VEERA REDDY CONTACT NO: 8106930204 Email:lomativeerareddy555@gmail.com PERSONNAL TRAITS of | Name | REDDY and Unmarried 2/44 DECLARATION I hereby declare that the above information mentioned is correct up to my knowledge and I the above infarmation mentioned is up my and bear the of the BANGALORE VEERA (LOMATI VEERA REDDY)", "tags": [{"Email": "lomativeerareddy555@gmail.com", "start_pos": 43, "end_pos": 72, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "lomativeerareddy555@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "L.VEERA REDDY", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 13, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "L.VEERA REDDY"}, {"Phone": "8106930204", "start_pos": 26, "end_pos": 36, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "8106930204"}, {"DOB": "2/44", "start_pos": 122, "end_pos": 126, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "2/44"}, {"PERSON": "VEERA (LOMATI VEERA REDDY)", "start_pos": 300, "end_pos": 326, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "VEERA (LOMATI VEERA REDDY)"}]}
{"line": "MRITYUNJAY UPADHYAY EMAIL : UPADHYAYMRITYUNJAY@GMAIL.COM MOBILE NO. : 7452806075 ADDRESS :C-60 MODINAGAR GHAZIABAD UP. Career objective   Date Of Birth: 01/01/1998  Permanent Address: Daffi near lanka B.H.U Varanasi,UP, PERSONAL DETAILS 221011.", "tags": [{"Email": "UPADHYAYMRITYUNJAY@GMAIL.COM", "start_pos": 28, "end_pos": 56, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "UPADHYAYMRITYUNJAY@GMAIL.COM"}, {"PERSON": "MRITYUNJAY UPADHYAY", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 19, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "MRITYUNJAY UPADHYAY"}, {"Phone": "7452806075", "start_pos": 70, "end_pos": 80, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "7452806075"}, {"DOB": "01/01/1998", "start_pos": 153, "end_pos": 163, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "01/01/1998"}]}
{"line": "YOGESH KUMAR BAGHEL Ph.No:-(+91)9812606059 Email:yogeshbaghel0712@gmail.com Present Address Vill:-Firozepur,Disti/Teh:-Palwal Palwal,H.R", "tags": [{"Email": "yogeshbaghel0712@gmail.com", "start_pos": 49, "end_pos": 75, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "yogeshbaghel0712@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "YOGESH KUMAR BAGHEL", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 19, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "YOGESH KUMAR BAGHEL"}]}
{"line": "Anish Kumar seeking an that me my my and broaden my Pedagantyada, Mob: Student Vishakhapatnam – 530044. Email id +91-9056559234 CAREER OBJECTIVE :moningianish@gmail.com %. 10th Pursued Pursued B.Tech Pursued with Specialization at “Narayana Junior College ” at at with 92 SKILLS from", "tags": [{"Email": "moningianish@gmail.com", "start_pos": 146, "end_pos": 168, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "moningianish@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Anish Kumar", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 11, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Anish Kumar"}, {"Phone": "+91-9056559234", "start_pos": 113, "end_pos": 127, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-9056559234"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.Tech", "start_pos": 193, "end_pos": 199, "tag": "EducationDegree", "type": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.Tech"}, {"ORG": "“Narayana Junior College", "start_pos": 231, "end_pos": 255, "tag": "ORG", "type": "ORG", "text": "“Narayana Junior College"}, {"CARDINAL": "92", "start_pos": 269, "end_pos": 271, "tag": "CARDINAL", "type": "CARDINAL", "text": "92"}]}
{"line": "M.GANESH Email:ganesh11061997@gmail.com Mobile: +91-9715791095 PERSONAL DETAIL  Father’s Name : Maivel.C HOBBIES: Date of Birth : 11-06-1997 Languages Known : Tamil, English Address : No.24/54, Pillaiyar kovil Street, Padikuppam, Koyembadu, Chennai-6060107", "tags": [{"Email": "ganesh11061997@gmail.com", "start_pos": 15, "end_pos": 39, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "ganesh11061997@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "M.GANESH", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 8, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "M.GANESH"}, {"Phone": "+91-9715791095", "start_pos": 48, "end_pos": 62, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-9715791095"}, {"DOB": "11-06-1997", "start_pos": 129, "end_pos": 139, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "11-06-1997"}]}
{"line": "AMAN KATIYAR Phone : +91 9149065796 Email :Amankatiyar73@gmail.com LinkedIn :https://www.linkedin.com/in/aman-katiyar- 011135171/GitHub :https://github.com/Kalphahoun  10-10-1998 PramodKumar SangeetaDevi OBC Male Indian WARD 34 KARIMNAGAR RAJPUR KANPURDEHAT. 9149065796 English,Hindi I declare that the details above are correct and true to the best of my knowledge", "tags": [{"Email": "Amankatiyar73@gmail.com", "start_pos": 43, "end_pos": 66, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Amankatiyar73@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "AMAN KATIYAR", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "AMAN KATIYAR"}, {"Phone": "9149065796", "start_pos": 25, "end_pos": 35, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9149065796"}, {"Phone": "011135171/GitHub", "start_pos": 119, "end_pos": 135, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "011135171/GitHub"}, {"DOB": "10-10-1998", "start_pos": 167, "end_pos": 177, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "10-10-1998"}, {"Phone": "9149065796", "start_pos": 258, "end_pos": 268, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9149065796"}]}
{"line": "Kapil Kushwah No, Type Nagar Contact No. : -7838094797, 8287593305 E-mail:-kapilkushwah05@gmail.com Permanent Address:- Type 2/95, Shastri Nagar Gwalior (M.P) DECLARATION  :- 20thJune 1994 Place: Date: :- English & Hindi :- Single :- Indian / Hindu", "tags": [{"Email": "-kapilkushwah05@gmail.com", "start_pos": 74, "end_pos": 99, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-kapilkushwah05@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Kapil Kushwah", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 13, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Kapil Kushwah"}, {"Phone": "-7838094797, 8287593305", "start_pos": 43, "end_pos": 66, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "-7838094797, 8287593305"}, {"DOB": "20thJune 1994", "start_pos": 174, "end_pos": 187, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "20thJune 1994"}]}
{"line": "TANNU KUMARI Permanent PLOT PRADESH MR. RAJPAL SINGH FEMALE 22-05-1997 Indian UNMarried CURRICULUM-VITAE Permanent Address:- PLOT NO:C-11,SECTOR-80,PHASE-2,CITY-NOIDA, UTTAR PRADESH Mob.No.: +919719790828 Email:Tannukumari2999@gmail.com OBJECTIVES: To pursue a career in an organization with my Principle, Discipline, Honesty, Hardworking for", "tags": [{"Email": "Tannukumari2999@gmail.com", "start_pos": 211, "end_pos": 236, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Tannukumari2999@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "TANNU KUMARI", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "TANNU KUMARI"}, {"DOB": "22-05-1997", "start_pos": 60, "end_pos": 70, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "22-05-1997"}, {"Phone": "+919719790828", "start_pos": 191, "end_pos": 204, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+919719790828"}]}
{"line": "VenkateswarluAdireddy : 91-9052629022 :venky.ar93@gmail.com Objective: Roles & Responsibilities:  Design Client-side architecture for UI development using Angular8. Description: Hote] project is for maintaining hotel bookings for guests. The main involved in are Room Management, Customer Management and Booking Calendar. ‘These are designed to administrative and manage customer receiving service and checking in new guests. (Venkateswarlu A)", "tags": [{"Email": "venky.ar93@gmail.com", "start_pos": 41, "end_pos": 61, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "venky.ar93@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "VenkateswarluAdireddy", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 21, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "VenkateswarluAdireddy"}, {"Phone": "91-9052629022", "start_pos": 25, "end_pos": 38, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "91-9052629022"}]}
{"line": "KAMALDEEP KAUR mailto:Kdbhupal9@gmail.com to-talk: +91 9460633694 PERSONAL PROFILE.  ➢ CONTACT NO. :- +91 9460633694 ➢ NATIONALITY: INDIAN ➢ MARITAL STATUS: -UNMARRIED ➢ NAME:- KAMALDEEP KAUR KAMALDEEP ➢ FNAME:- SHRI. SUKHMAHENDER SINGH ➢ MOTHER’S NAME:- SMT. GURPREET KAUR ➢ DOB:- SEPTEMBER16-1995 ➢ ADDRESS:-Sec no.6, Ward no.43,Hanumangarh Jn District: Hanumangarh (Raj)", "tags": [{"Email": "Kdbhupal9@gmail.com", "start_pos": 22, "end_pos": 41, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Kdbhupal9@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "KAMALDEEP KAUR", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 14, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "KAMALDEEP KAUR"}, {"Phone": "9460633694", "start_pos": 55, "end_pos": 65, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9460633694"}, {"Phone": "9460633694", "start_pos": 105, "end_pos": 115, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9460633694"}, {"PERSON": "KAMALDEEP KAUR KAMALDEEP", "start_pos": 176, "end_pos": 200, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "KAMALDEEP KAUR KAMALDEEP"}, {"DOB": "SEPTEMBER16-1995", "start_pos": 281, "end_pos": 297, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "SEPTEMBER16-1995"}]}
{"line": "RESUME E_MAIL I D:swatimayeerath97@gmail.com PHONE NO.:9776672278 Name:SWATIMAYEE RATH C/O: RAJANI KANT RATH B-38, Near Mother dairy, Sec -15, Noida-201301 P ERSONAL DETAILS: Nationality Gender Marital Status Languages known : Indian : May 23, 1997 : Female : Unmarried : English, Hindi & Oriya Declaration: Date: Place:Noida I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge. Swatimayee Rath ", "tags": [{"Email": "swatimayeerath97@gmail.com", "start_pos": 18, "end_pos": 44, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "swatimayeerath97@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "RATH", "start_pos": 82, "end_pos": 86, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "RATH"}, {"DOB": "May 23, 1997", "start_pos": 236, "end_pos": 248, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "May 23, 1997"}, {"PERSON": "Swatimayee Rath", "start_pos": 417, "end_pos": 432, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Swatimayee Rath"}]}
{"line": "BARSHA KUMARI ADD:BANGALURU ,KARNATAKA-562106 E-MAIL ID:varshababul16@gmail.com Mob:8210952382 PERSONAL PROFILE Name : Barsha kumari Date of Birth : 31/12/1998 Gender : Female Nationality : Indian Board/University CBSE BIHAR BOARD BANGALURU year", "tags": [{"Email": "varshababul16@gmail.com", "start_pos": 56, "end_pos": 79, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "varshababul16@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "BARSHA KUMARI", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 13, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "BARSHA KUMARI"}, {"PERSON": "Barsha kumari", "start_pos": 119, "end_pos": 132, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Barsha kumari"}, {"DOB": "31/12/1998", "start_pos": 149, "end_pos": 159, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "31/12/1998"}]}
{"line": "Rashi chouksey Information technology engineering Email Id:-khushichouksey148@gmail.com Phone No.:-7987686183 Carrier Objective:-  e Permanent Address: Main market bargi nagar jabalpur, Madhya Pradesh Linkedin Link:- https://www.linkedin.com/in/rashi-chouksey- Oab10b1a5 DECLARATION:- | hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to best of my knowledge. Place Date CURRICULUM VITAE Rashi chouksey Information technology engineering Email Id:-khushichouksey148@gmail.com Phone No.:-7987686183 Carrier Objective:- e To secure a position where | can efficiently contribute my skills and abilities to the growth of the organization and build my professional career. Academic Details:- e Completed Bachelor of Engineering from shri ram institute of technology Collage Affiliated To Rajiv Gandhi Praudyoiki Vishvavidyalaya Bhopal with CGPA 6.56 in 2019 e Completed Higher Secondary Education from Madhya Pradesh Board Of Secondary Education with 6.66 in 2015. e Completed High School Education from Madhya Pradesh Board Of Secondary Education with 6.8 in 2013. Training:- Personal Profile:-  e Father Name : Mr. Sharad chouksey e Permanent Address: Main market bargi nagar jabalpur, Madhya Pradesh Linkedin Link:- https://www.linkedin.com/in/rashi-chouksey- Oab10b1a5 DECLARATION:- | hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to best of my knowledge. Place e Date of Birth : Aug 23, 1998 e Marital Statu : UnMarried e Religion : Hindu e Nationality : Indian e Languages Known : English, Hindi e Current Address : Indore,Madhya Pradesh Date", "tags": [{"Email": "-khushichouksey148@gmail.com", "start_pos": 459, "end_pos": 487, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-khushichouksey148@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Rashi chouksey", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 14, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Rashi chouksey"}, {"GPE": "Madhya Pradesh", "start_pos": 185, "end_pos": 199, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Madhya Pradesh"}, {"EducationDegree": "Bachelor of Engineering", "start_pos": 710, "end_pos": 733, "tag": "EducationDegree", "type": "EducationDegree", "text": "Bachelor of Engineering"}, {"ORG": "shri ram institute of technology Collage Affiliated To Rajiv Gandhi Praudyoiki Vishvavidyalaya Bhopal", "start_pos": 739, "end_pos": 840, "tag": "ORG", "type": "ORG", "text": "shri ram institute of technology Collage Affiliated To Rajiv Gandhi Praudyoiki Vishvavidyalaya Bhopal"}, {"CARDINAL": "6.56", "start_pos": 851, "end_pos": 855, "tag": "CARDINAL", "type": "CARDINAL", "text": "6.56"}, {"DATE": "2019", "start_pos": 859, "end_pos": 863, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "2019"}, {"CARDINAL": "6.66", "start_pos": 957, "end_pos": 961, "tag": "CARDINAL", "type": "CARDINAL", "text": "6.66"}, {"CARDINAL": "6.8", "start_pos": 1059, "end_pos": 1062, "tag": "CARDINAL", "type": "CARDINAL", "text": "6.8"}, {"DOB": "Aug 23, 1998", "start_pos": 1403, "end_pos": 1415, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "Aug 23, 1998"}, {"GPE": "Indore,Madhya Pradesh", "start_pos": 1541, "end_pos": 1562, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Indore,Madhya Pradesh"}]}
{"line": "Curriculum Vitaé Name : Pooja Kumari Address E-mail : Pooja kumari c/o:-Abhishek jewellers (Kati Factory Road,Mahtma Gandhi Nagar) P.O:-Bahadurpur houshing colony,PS:-Patrakar Nagar Mobile No : 6205011158 :pv3150172@gmail.com Career Objective: Challenging Career In Professionally Managed Industry  : 30/06/1996 : Female Languages Known : English ,Hindi DATE: 15/06/2020 Signature", "tags": [{"Email": "pv3150172@gmail.com", "start_pos": 206, "end_pos": 225, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "pv3150172@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Pooja Kumari", "start_pos": 24, "end_pos": 36, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Pooja Kumari"}, {"PERSON": "Pooja kumari", "start_pos": 54, "end_pos": 66, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Pooja kumari"}, {"Phone": "6205011158", "start_pos": 194, "end_pos": 204, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "6205011158"}, {"DOB": "30/06/1996", "start_pos": 300, "end_pos": 310, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "30/06/1996"}, {"DOB": "15/06/2020", "start_pos": 359, "end_pos": 369, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "15/06/2020"}]}
{"line": "KISHAN KUMAR Email:kishanraj012345@gmail.com Mobile: +91-8210883848, 7282833242", "tags": [{"Email": "kishanraj012345@gmail.com", "start_pos": 19, "end_pos": 44, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "kishanraj012345@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "KISHAN KUMAR", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "KISHAN KUMAR"}, {"Phone": "+91-8210883848, 7282833242", "start_pos": 53, "end_pos": 79, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-8210883848, 7282833242"}]}
{"line": "Ayushi Rastogi A-L-64, Deen Dayal Nagar, MDA Moradabad, Uttar Pradesh Pincode-244001 CONTACT NO- +91-9568642040 E-MAIL –aayushi.r79@gmail.com OBJECTIVE:   Date of Birth : 7th January, 1996.  Father’s Name: Nileshwar Rastogi  Nationality : Indian  Marital Status : Single  Interests : Badminton, Novels, Dance, Fitness, Fashion (AYUSHI RASTOGI) Date: PUBLIC - Page 2 of 2", "tags": [{"Email": "aayushi.r79@gmail.com", "start_pos": 120, "end_pos": 141, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "aayushi.r79@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Ayushi Rastogi", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 14, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Ayushi Rastogi"}, {"GPE": "Moradabad, Uttar Pradesh", "start_pos": 45, "end_pos": 69, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Moradabad, Uttar Pradesh"}, {"Phone": "+91-9568642040", "start_pos": 97, "end_pos": 111, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-9568642040"}, {"DOB": "7th January, 1996.", "start_pos": 171, "end_pos": 189, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "7th January, 1996."}]}
{"line": "Kawade Gitanjali Vikram Email ID:-kawadegitanjali1596@gmail.com Contact No:-8806691249 OBJECTIVE:  : 3 April 1996 : Indian : Marathi, Hindi, English. : Quick Learner, Positive Thinking.  : At.Golangri, Post.Chausala, Tal.Beed, Dist. Beed, 431122. I Miss. Gitanjali Vikram Kawade, here by declare that the information provided above is true to the best of", "tags": [{"Email": "-kawadegitanjali1596@gmail.com", "start_pos": 33, "end_pos": 63, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-kawadegitanjali1596@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Kawade Gitanjali Vikram", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 23, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Kawade Gitanjali Vikram"}, {"DOB": "3 April 1996", "start_pos": 100, "end_pos": 112, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "3 April 1996"}, {"PERSON": "Gitanjali Vikram Kawade,", "start_pos": 253, "end_pos": 277, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Gitanjali Vikram Kawade,"}]}
{"line": "Ashwini B. Khobragade Contact: +91-7057323991 Email:-ashwinikhobragade760@gmail.com LinkedIn Profile:-https://www.linkedin.com/in/ashwini -khobragade-90a828158 Present Address: - Pratap Nagar, Dist:Nagpur(Maharashtra) postal code: 440009 DECLARATION  PLACE:Nagpur DATE: Miss Ashwini Khobragade I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.", "tags": [{"Email": "-ashwinikhobragade760@gmail.com", "start_pos": 52, "end_pos": 83, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-ashwinikhobragade760@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Ashwini B. Khobragade", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 21, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Ashwini B. Khobragade"}, {"Phone": "+91-7057323991", "start_pos": 31, "end_pos": 45, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-7057323991"}, {"PERSON": "Ashwini Khobragade", "start_pos": 274, "end_pos": 292, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Ashwini Khobragade"}]}
{"line": "Name – SANDEEP KUMAR Mobile No:- 9956510868 E-mail- SK9956510868@gmail.com Profile – Java developer (Fresher) Times New Roman Father’s Name Mr. Sanjay Kumar Name Date of Birth Marital Status Nationality Languages Permanent Mr. Sanjay Kumar 15-08-1994 Single Indian English, Lal Caloni Kanpur, (U.P)", "tags": [{"Email": "SK9956510868@gmail.com", "start_pos": 52, "end_pos": 74, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "SK9956510868@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SANDEEP KUMAR", "start_pos": 7, "end_pos": 20, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SANDEEP KUMAR"}, {"Phone": "9956510868", "start_pos": 33, "end_pos": 43, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9956510868"}, {"Phone": "SK9956510868@gmail.com", "start_pos": 52, "end_pos": 74, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "SK9956510868@gmail.com"}, {"Designation": "Java developer", "start_pos": 85, "end_pos": 99, "tag": "Designation", "type": "Designation", "text": "Java developer"}, {"DOB": "15-08-1994", "start_pos": 240, "end_pos": 250, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "15-08-1994"}]}
{"line": "Anuj Kumar  Cell: +91-8953642581 67 Pocket-5, Mayur Vihar Phase-1, New Delhi Email:anuj1105sharma@gmail.co m Personal Details  Name : Anuj Kumar Date of Birth : 08 December 1998 Nationality : Indian Language : Hindi, English  Father's Hometown 97, Old Market hereby declare that the information above is complete and true to be best of my knowledge. Place: Delhi Place: Delhi (Anuj Kumar)", "tags": [{"Email": "anuj1105sharma@gmail.co", "start_pos": 83, "end_pos": 106, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "anuj1105sharma@gmail.co"}, {"PERSON": "Anuj Kumar", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 10, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Anuj Kumar"}, {"Phone": "+91-8953642581", "start_pos": 17, "end_pos": 31, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-8953642581"}, {"GPE": "New Delhi", "start_pos": 66, "end_pos": 75, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "New Delhi"}, {"PERSON": "Anuj Kumar", "start_pos": 132, "end_pos": 142, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Anuj Kumar"}, {"DOB": "08 December 1998", "start_pos": 159, "end_pos": 175, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "08 December 1998"}, {"GPE": "Delhi", "start_pos": 367, "end_pos": 372, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Delhi"}, {"PERSON": "(Anuj Kumar)", "start_pos": 373, "end_pos": 385, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "(Anuj Kumar)"}]}
{"line": "RESUME PRADNYA BALASO PATIL FRESHER Phone No :(+91)8975531377 E-mail :pradnyapatil2894@gmail.com Date of Birth :25-11-1995 Address :New Sanghvi, Pune __________________________________________________________________________________________________", "tags": [{"Email": "pradnyapatil2894@gmail.com", "start_pos": 70, "end_pos": 96, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "pradnyapatil2894@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "PRADNYA BALASO PATIL FRESHER", "start_pos": 7, "end_pos": 35, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "PRADNYA BALASO PATIL FRESHER"}, {"Phone": ":(+91)8975531377", "start_pos": 45, "end_pos": 61, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": ":(+91)8975531377"}, {"GPE": "Pune", "start_pos": 145, "end_pos": 149, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Pune"}]}
{"line": "Afsar Ahmad  Khanak017860@gmail.com +91 8882475525 Personal Details:  Father’s Name : Mr. Firoj Ahmad  Mother’s Name : Mrs. Neha Firoz Address : 4th floor front, E-119, Hari kothi, Abul Fazal Enclave,Jamia Nagar, New Delhi- 110025. Passport no.:-Applied for    Permanent Address : House no. 5, Beside Muner chakki, Mohalla Goriyana, Bhadohi 221401 Languages: English, Hindi    Date Of Birth : 3 july 1998 I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge & belief. Afsar Ahmad", "tags": [{"Email": "Khanak017860@gmail.com", "start_pos": 13, "end_pos": 35, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Khanak017860@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Afsar Ahmad Khanak017860@gmail.com", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 34, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Afsar Ahmad Khanak017860@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "8882475525", "start_pos": 39, "end_pos": 49, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "8882475525"}, {"GPE": "New Delhi-", "start_pos": 214, "end_pos": 224, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "New Delhi-"}, {"DOB": "3 july 1998", "start_pos": 398, "end_pos": 409, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "3 july 1998"}, {"PERSON": "Afsar Ahmad", "start_pos": 510, "end_pos": 521, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Afsar Ahmad"}]}
{"line": "Preeti Tiwari Address: 8/285, Dr Ambedkar Nagar, Sec VI +91-9910266706|preetitiwari0022@gmail.com", "tags": [{"Email": "preetitiwari0022@gmail.com", "start_pos": 71, "end_pos": 97, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "preetitiwari0022@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Preeti Tiwari", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 13, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Preeti Tiwari"}, {"Phone": "+91-9910266706|preetitiwari0022@gmail.com", "start_pos": 56, "end_pos": 97, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-9910266706|preetitiwari0022@gmail.com"}]}
{"line": "RESUME DEEPAK KUMAR YADAV Languages: English , Hindi ADDRESS:- H NO.36 High Parvarpara ,Sikandarpur Basti, UP 272129 :iamroyaldk19@gmail.com:+91-9793892775 Birth: 15/Sept/ 1997; CARRIER OBJECTIVE:", "tags": [{"Email": "iamroyaldk19@gmail.com", "start_pos": 119, "end_pos": 141, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "iamroyaldk19@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "DEEPAK KUMAR YADAV", "start_pos": 7, "end_pos": 25, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "DEEPAK KUMAR YADAV"}, {"DOB": "15/Sept/ 1997;", "start_pos": 165, "end_pos": 179, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "15/Sept/ 1997;"}]}
{"line": "S EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS QUALIFICATIONS S EDUCATIONAL HARSH KANDARI CONTACT CAREER OBJECTIVE E-mail:Harshkandari66@gmail.com Phone:8130069943 Address: Kh No.4/15-16,Block D,Street No.7,Tomar Colony,Burari,Delhi 110084", "tags": [{"Email": "Harshkandari66@gmail.com", "start_pos": 104, "end_pos": 128, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Harshkandari66@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "HARSH KANDARI", "start_pos": 58, "end_pos": 71, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "HARSH KANDARI"}]}
{"line": "MOHAMMAD QASIM Mobile:- 08859228213 Email ID:-pashaqasim027@gmail.com Address: C-256A, Shaheenbagh, Jamia Nagar, Okhla New Delhi. PERSONAL DETAILS  Permanent Address : Village Asgaripur, House No 19, Post Joya, Date of Birth Father’s Name Sex Marital Status Nationality Languages Known Amroha (U.P) 244222 Mohammad Warik Male Single Indian Hindi, English & Urdu : 07/08/1994 : : : : :", "tags": [{"Email": "-pashaqasim027@gmail.com", "start_pos": 45, "end_pos": 69, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-pashaqasim027@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "MOHAMMAD QASIM", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 14, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "MOHAMMAD QASIM"}, {"Phone": "08859228213", "start_pos": 24, "end_pos": 35, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "08859228213"}, {"GPE": "Okhla New Delhi.", "start_pos": 113, "end_pos": 129, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Okhla New Delhi."}, {"DOB": "07/08/1994", "start_pos": 363, "end_pos": 373, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "07/08/1994"}]}
{"line": "Yogesh kumar Bsc.(electronics houners) Phone : +91 –7065769553 Email :yogeshsingh4340@gmail.com Address :RZ-16A/284 galino.-2 west sagarpur new delhi-46 ----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------", "tags": [{"Email": "yogeshsingh4340@gmail.com", "start_pos": 70, "end_pos": 95, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "yogeshsingh4340@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Yogesh kumar", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Yogesh kumar"}, {"EducationDegree": "Bsc.(electronics", "start_pos": 13, "end_pos": 29, "tag": "EducationDegree", "type": "EducationDegree", "text": "Bsc.(electronics"}, {"Phone": "–7065769553", "start_pos": 51, "end_pos": 62, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "–7065769553"}]}
{"line": "Swaroop Singh Rathore Ajmer, Rajasthan Email:swarooprathore70@gmail.com H.No:-4/134, Panchsheel Nagar B-Block, Mob:-8619197230, 09929999049  DETAILS: Name Lal Bahadur Singh Rathore Date of English &", "tags": [{"Email": "swarooprathore70@gmail.com", "start_pos": 45, "end_pos": 71, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "swarooprathore70@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Swaroop Singh Rathore", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 21, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Swaroop Singh Rathore"}, {"GPE": "Ajmer, Rajasthan", "start_pos": 22, "end_pos": 38, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Ajmer, Rajasthan"}, {"Phone": "09929999049", "start_pos": 128, "end_pos": 139, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "09929999049"}]}
{"line": "CURRICULUM VITAE MOBILE 9118314787 E-MAIL-dipaliofficial1@gmail.com LINKED-INUrl- www.linkedin.com/in/dipali-baranwal-880319161 Personal Detail Date of Birth Father’s Name Mother’s Name : 11-june-1998 : Mr. Santosh Baranwal : Mrs. Sunita Baranwal Permanent Address : CK. 49/80 ‘B’ Bhuletan , Varanasi Current Address : A 121 BEL Colony, BrijVihar , Ghaziyabad Nationality Gender : Indian : Female Language Known : English & Hindi Hobbies", "tags": [{"Email": "E-MAIL-dipaliofficial1@gmail.com", "start_pos": 35, "end_pos": 67, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "E-MAIL-dipaliofficial1@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "9118314787", "start_pos": 24, "end_pos": 34, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9118314787"}, {"DOB": "11-june-1998", "start_pos": 188, "end_pos": 200, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "11-june-1998"}]}
{"line": "CURRICULAM VITAE Bandana Kumari Saw Email –bandanasaw302@gmail.com Contact No :+ 91-7004080674  Feb 1990 3rd Baldeo Saw Female Single Indian Languages: English and Hindi Hobbies: Contact:", "tags": [{"Email": "bandanasaw302@gmail.com", "start_pos": 43, "end_pos": 66, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "bandanasaw302@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Bandana Kumari Saw", "start_pos": 17, "end_pos": 35, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Bandana Kumari Saw"}, {"Phone": "91-7004080674", "start_pos": 81, "end_pos": 94, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "91-7004080674"}, {"DOB": "Feb 1990 3rd", "start_pos": 95, "end_pos": 107, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "Feb 1990 3rd"}]}
{"line": "NITI PANDEY Phone : 7897105970 E-mail : 1121nitipandey@gmail.com SUMMARY EXPERIENCE PERSONAL PROFILE D/o: Mr. Ashok Pandey DOB: 15TH January 1998 daydays) Language Known: English,Hindi Address: Whitefield ,Bengaluru ,Karnataka. ACHIEVEMENTS • • • •", "tags": [{"Email": "1121nitipandey@gmail.com", "start_pos": 40, "end_pos": 64, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "1121nitipandey@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "NITI PANDEY", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 11, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "NITI PANDEY"}, {"Phone": "7897105970", "start_pos": 20, "end_pos": 30, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "7897105970"}, {"Phone": "1121nitipandey@gmail.com", "start_pos": 40, "end_pos": 64, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "1121nitipandey@gmail.com"}, {"DOB": "15TH January 1998 daydays)", "start_pos": 128, "end_pos": 154, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "15TH January 1998 daydays)"}]}
{"line": "SUPRIYA SAMANTA Email:supriyosamanta18cool@gmail.com Contact No. : +919330773549 +919564224731 PERSONAL INFORMATION 02/07/1997 Father’s Name Date of Birth Samar Samanta Hindi- Speak Nationality Religion Sex Marital Status Language known : : : : : Indian Hindu Male Un-married Permanent Address : Jujersha ,Howrah Bengali-Read, Write, Speak English- Read, Write, Speak", "tags": [{"Email": "supriyosamanta18cool@gmail.com", "start_pos": 22, "end_pos": 52, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "supriyosamanta18cool@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SUPRIYA SAMANTA", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 15, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SUPRIYA SAMANTA"}, {"Phone": "+919330773549 +919564224731", "start_pos": 67, "end_pos": 94, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+919330773549 +919564224731"}, {"DOB": "02/07/1997", "start_pos": 116, "end_pos": 126, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "02/07/1997"}]}
{"line": "VIJETA SINGH THAKUR Email :vijeta1996thakur@gmail.com Contact No: 9977512007 Personal Details  Gender: Female. Date of Marital status:  Linguistic Skills: Hindi, English.  Location: Bhopal.  Date of birth: 24/05/1996.", "tags": [{"Email": "vijeta1996thakur@gmail.com", "start_pos": 27, "end_pos": 53, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "vijeta1996thakur@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "VIJETA SINGH THAKUR", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 19, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "VIJETA SINGH THAKUR"}, {"Phone": "9977512007", "start_pos": 66, "end_pos": 76, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9977512007"}, {"DOB": "24/05/1996.", "start_pos": 210, "end_pos": 221, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "24/05/1996."}]}
{"line": "Resume MrunaliAuchar At.postAmbheri, Tal.koregaon, Dist.Satara Pin Code:415511 Maharashtra, India Email:mrunalia1996@gmail.com Mobile:8379892038", "tags": [{"Email": "mrunalia1996@gmail.com", "start_pos": 104, "end_pos": 126, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "mrunalia1996@gmail.com"}, {"GPE": "Maharashtra, India", "start_pos": 79, "end_pos": 97, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Maharashtra, India"}]}
{"line": "LOKESH.S 2/83, Ntr Circle, Zuzuvadi, Hosur, Tamilnadu-26 Mobile: 8903169650 E-Mail:slokesh2912@gmail.com", "tags": [{"Email": "slokesh2912@gmail.com", "start_pos": 83, "end_pos": 104, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "slokesh2912@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "LOKESH.S", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 8, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "LOKESH.S"}, {"Phone": "8903169650", "start_pos": 65, "end_pos": 75, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "8903169650"}]}
{"line": "JANGAM VEERESH KUMAR H-N0:166, Bn Reddy Nagar LB Nagar Hyderabad-500070. Email:veereshkumarj2020@gmail.com Contact:+(91) 9493375079 PERSONAL PROFILE:  Fathers Name : Jangam Koteshwaraiah Date Of Birth : 20 June 1999 Nationality : Indian Languages Known : Telugu, English", "tags": [{"Email": "veereshkumarj2020@gmail.com", "start_pos": 79, "end_pos": 106, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "veereshkumarj2020@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "JANGAM VEERESH KUMAR", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 20, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "JANGAM VEERESH KUMAR"}, {"Phone": "9493375079", "start_pos": 121, "end_pos": 131, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9493375079"}, {"DOB": "20 June 1999", "start_pos": 202, "end_pos": 214, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "20 June 1999"}]}
{"line": "KOMAL GABA CONTACT: +91-7404111804 EMAIL:khuranakomal10@gmail.com PERSONAL DETAILS   Father name: Mr. Rajender Khurana  Husband name: Mr. Kumar Gaba  Languages Known: English, Hindi, Punjabi  Marital Status: Married  Nationality: Indian  Strength: Adaptable, Confident.  Permanent Address: WZ-8, Second Floor, Meenakshi Garden, Near Subhash Nagar Metro Station, New Delhi(110018)  Date of Birth: 07 Oct 1993", "tags": [{"Email": "khuranakomal10@gmail.com", "start_pos": 41, "end_pos": 65, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "khuranakomal10@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "KOMAL GABA", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 10, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "KOMAL GABA"}, {"Phone": "+91-7404111804", "start_pos": 20, "end_pos": 34, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-7404111804"}, {"GPE": "New Delhi(110018)", "start_pos": 368, "end_pos": 385, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "New Delhi(110018)"}, {"DOB": "07 Oct 1993", "start_pos": 403, "end_pos": 414, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "07 Oct 1993"}]}
{"line": "SAMARTH SALUJA RAJAT VIHAR SEC-62 NOIDA 201301 EMAIL:-SAMARTHSALUJA24@GMAIL.COM PHONE NO:-9205874023", "tags": [{"Email": "-SAMARTHSALUJA24@GMAIL.COM", "start_pos": 53, "end_pos": 79, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-SAMARTHSALUJA24@GMAIL.COM"}, {"PERSON": "SAMARTH SALUJA RAJAT VIHAR", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 26, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SAMARTH SALUJA RAJAT VIHAR"}, {"GPE": "NOIDA", "start_pos": 34, "end_pos": 39, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "NOIDA"}, {"Phone": "NO:-9205874023", "start_pos": 86, "end_pos": 100, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "NO:-9205874023"}]}
{"line": "KUMARI NIRUPAMA SINHA gmail of level with a which helps my and Email id:-nirupamasinha37a@gmail.com Mobile no:-8744810163 PERSONAL DETAILS : 01st February 1998 Date of Birth Languages Know : Hindi, English Contact Address : B88,Rama Park , Uttam Nagar ,New Delhi", "tags": [{"Email": "-nirupamasinha37a@gmail.com", "start_pos": 72, "end_pos": 99, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-nirupamasinha37a@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "KUMARI NIRUPAMA SINHA", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 21, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "KUMARI NIRUPAMA SINHA"}, {"DOB": "01st February 1998", "start_pos": 141, "end_pos": 159, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "01st February 1998"}, {"GPE": "Delhi", "start_pos": 257, "end_pos": 262, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Delhi"}]}
{"line": "RESUME BHUPENDRA NAMDEO SEWAK PARK DWARKA MORH METRO STATION DELHI - 110059. Solarsystems1992@gmail.com Mobile: 8305003031, 7303250575. Personal details  BHUPENDRA NAMDEO NAME MERITAL STATUS SINGLE FATHER‟S NAME Mr. SHANKAR NAMDEO MOTHER‟S NAME Mrs. MAMTA NAMDEO DATE OF BIRTH 05TH JAN 1992 GENDER MALE NATIONALITY INDIAN LANGUAGES KNOWN HINDI, ENGLISH DECLARATION:- I hereby declare that the all information are true & correct of best of my knowledge and belief. Date: - / / Place: -NEW DELHI (BHUPENDRA NAMDEO) Signature: -", "tags": [{"Email": "Solarsystems1992@gmail.com", "start_pos": 77, "end_pos": 103, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Solarsystems1992@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "BHUPENDRA NAMDEO SEWAK", "start_pos": 7, "end_pos": 29, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "BHUPENDRA NAMDEO SEWAK"}, {"Phone": "8305003031, 7303250575.", "start_pos": 112, "end_pos": 135, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "8305003031, 7303250575."}, {"DOB": "BIRTH 05TH JAN 1992", "start_pos": 270, "end_pos": 289, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "BIRTH 05TH JAN 1992"}]}
{"line": "Aug 2016– Present Expected Graduation: AUGUST 2020 83 percent 10/10 CGPA SUNIL MISHRA NewDelhi |sm6729933@gmail.com| +91-8510984226 EDUCATION Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University, New Delhi,India Maharaja Surajmal Institute of Technology", "tags": [{"Email": "sm6729933@gmail.com", "start_pos": 96, "end_pos": 115, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "sm6729933@gmail.com"}, {"DATE": "Aug 2016– Present", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 17, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "Aug 2016– Present"}, {"DATE": "AUGUST 2020", "start_pos": 39, "end_pos": 50, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "AUGUST 2020"}, {"CARDINAL": "83 percent 10/10", "start_pos": 51, "end_pos": 67, "tag": "CARDINAL", "type": "CARDINAL", "text": "83 percent 10/10"}, {"Phone": "+91-8510984226", "start_pos": 117, "end_pos": 131, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-8510984226"}, {"ORG": "Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University, New Delhi,India Maharaja Surajmal Institute of Technology", "start_pos": 142, "end_pos": 242, "tag": "ORG", "type": "ORG", "text": "Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University, New Delhi,India Maharaja Surajmal Institute of Technology"}]}
{"line": "HIMALAYA RAJ Vill-Ismailpur BIJNOR-246725 CONTACT NO: - 9045396373 E-MAIL ID:-honeychaudhary185@gmail.com • B.Sc. (2013- 2016) from MJPRU University with Second Division.", "tags": [{"Email": "-honeychaudhary185@gmail.com", "start_pos": 77, "end_pos": 105, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-honeychaudhary185@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "HIMALAYA RAJ Vill-Ismailpur", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 27, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "HIMALAYA RAJ Vill-Ismailpur"}, {"Phone": "9045396373", "start_pos": 56, "end_pos": 66, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9045396373"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.Sc.", "start_pos": 108, "end_pos": 113, "tag": "EducationDegree", "type": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.Sc."}, {"DATE": "(2013- 2016)", "start_pos": 114, "end_pos": 126, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "(2013- 2016)"}, {"ORG": "MJPRU University", "start_pos": 132, "end_pos": 148, "tag": "ORG", "type": "ORG", "text": "MJPRU University"}]}
{"line": "Sakshi Gupta Mobile No.:9981725376 Email id:sakshigupta04031999@gmail.com Gender:Female Language:English", "tags": [{"Email": "sakshigupta04031999@gmail.com", "start_pos": 44, "end_pos": 73, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "sakshigupta04031999@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Sakshi Gupta", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Sakshi Gupta"}]}
{"line": "Shivam Rai H.No-10 Gali No -1 Acharya Puri Sector 12 Near By Bus Stand Gurugram 122001 Email ID:Shivamrai25061997@gmail.com Mobile No. – 7905278752 ,9169169845  25-06-1997 Ajay Rai Watching Movies Internet Surfing. Hindi, English DECLARATION “I hereby by declare that all the information give above are true, correct, and best of my Knowledge.” Date: Place: (Shivam Rai) Shivam Rai H.No-10 Gali No -1 Acharya Puri Sector 12 Near By Bus Stand Gurugram 122001 Email ID:Shivamrai25061997@gmail.com Mobile No. – 7905278752 ,9169169845 CAREER OBJECTIVE “To secure a challenging position where I can effectively contribute my skills, and innovative ideas to gain knowledge in the work-oriented environment.” TECHNICAL QUALIFICATION Qualification Institute University Qualification Institute University", "tags": [{"Email": "Shivamrai25061997@gmail.com", "start_pos": 467, "end_pos": 494, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Shivamrai25061997@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Shivam Rai", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 10, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Shivam Rai"}, {"Phone": "7905278752", "start_pos": 137, "end_pos": 147, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "7905278752"}, {"DOB": "25-06-1997", "start_pos": 160, "end_pos": 170, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "25-06-1997"}, {"PERSON": "Ajay Rai", "start_pos": 171, "end_pos": 179, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Ajay Rai"}]}
{"line": "PHP PROGRAMMER PERSONAL INFORMATION Name- Mahir Siddiqui Email-mahirsiddiqui5@gmail.com Phone-9897700503 Address- Town Nakur Dist.Saharanpur Uttar Pradesh(INDIA)", "tags": [{"Email": "Email-mahirsiddiqui5@gmail.com", "start_pos": 57, "end_pos": 87, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Email-mahirsiddiqui5@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Mahir Siddiqui", "start_pos": 42, "end_pos": 56, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Mahir Siddiqui"}]}
{"line": "Namrata Chouhan 5-87 patel colony , Indore Contact no. : +916261095196 Email id:namratachouhan376@gmail.com : Declaration: Declaration: : march 1997 Female Indian Hindi, English Hindi Mr. Dilip singh chouhan In Process Date:../../2019 Place: Indore", "tags": [{"Email": "namratachouhan376@gmail.com", "start_pos": 80, "end_pos": 107, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "namratachouhan376@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Namrata Chouhan", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 15, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Namrata Chouhan"}, {"GPE": "Indore", "start_pos": 36, "end_pos": 42, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Indore"}, {"Phone": "+916261095196", "start_pos": 57, "end_pos": 70, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+916261095196"}, {"DOB": "march 1997", "start_pos": 138, "end_pos": 148, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "march 1997"}, {"GPE": "Indore", "start_pos": 242, "end_pos": 248, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Indore"}]}
{"line": "declare that the information given above is and best of my knowledge & Place: {SUMIT KUMAR) Address: C-1/249A, Gali No-13, Harsh Vihar, Delhi-110093 Contact No.:- 8587022754,9289206700 Email Id:sumitmdkashyap@gmail.com RESUME PERSONAL DETAILS Address: Harsh Vihar, Email Father’s name Date of birth Gender Marital status Nationality Languages Known : Fathers name Date of Religion Languages Mr. Pramod and English", "tags": [{"Email": "sumitmdkashyap@gmail.com", "start_pos": 194, "end_pos": 218, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "sumitmdkashyap@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "{SUMIT KUMAR)", "start_pos": 78, "end_pos": 91, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "{SUMIT KUMAR)"}, {"Phone": "8587022754,9289206700", "start_pos": 163, "end_pos": 184, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "8587022754,9289206700"}]}
{"line": "VAMSIKRISHNA MULLAPUDI E-mail:mullapudivamsichowdary@gmail.com S/oSrinu mullapudi Phone no: 8919811383 Duddukuru,DevarapalliMandal Andhra Pradesh – 534313.", "tags": [{"Email": "mullapudivamsichowdary@gmail.com", "start_pos": 30, "end_pos": 62, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "mullapudivamsichowdary@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "VAMSIKRISHNA MULLAPUDI", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 22, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "VAMSIKRISHNA MULLAPUDI"}, {"Phone": "8919811383", "start_pos": 92, "end_pos": 102, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "8919811383"}, {"GPE": "Duddukuru,DevarapalliMandal Andhra Pradesh", "start_pos": 103, "end_pos": 145, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Duddukuru,DevarapalliMandal Andhra Pradesh"}, {"Phone": "534313.", "start_pos": 148, "end_pos": 155, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "534313."}]}
{"line": "BHARTI Vermab938@gmail.com +91 7973256547 Khanauri Distt.sangrur Punjab 148027 D.O.B : August 05,1997 Languages:English,HindiPunjabi OBJECTIVE", "tags": [{"Email": "Vermab938@gmail.com", "start_pos": 7, "end_pos": 26, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Vermab938@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "BHARTI Vermab938@gmail.com", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 26, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "BHARTI Vermab938@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "7973256547", "start_pos": 31, "end_pos": 41, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "7973256547"}, {"DOB": "August 05,1997", "start_pos": 87, "end_pos": 101, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "August 05,1997"}]}
{"line": "Shashank Pateriya RESUME Address :H-no 58sonagiri-c-sector Bhopal (M.P) 462021 Mobile :+918435520792 Email :shashankpateriya786@gmail.com   Date Of Birth – 20/12/1996  Fathers Name – Chandra shekharpateriya  Mother Name – Mamtapateriya  Permanent Address – 89,simariya,village simariya, TehsilDeori,District-sagar(MP)470226  Nationality – Indian  Language Known – English and Hindi", "tags": [{"Email": "shashankpateriya786@gmail.com", "start_pos": 108, "end_pos": 137, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "shashankpateriya786@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Shashank Pateriya", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 17, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Shashank Pateriya"}, {"GPE": "Bhopal", "start_pos": 59, "end_pos": 65, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Bhopal"}, {"DOB": "20/12/1996", "start_pos": 156, "end_pos": 166, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "20/12/1996"}]}
{"line": "SOURABH SHARMA E-Mail: 18041997sh@gmail.com August 26, 2020 RE: Android Application Developer, Dear Sir/Madam, I was motivated to contact you upon learning that Excellence Technosoft Private Limited has an opening for a new Android Application Developer. For several years now, I have focused my career path and academic pursuits on learning and developing those all-important skills necessary to be great in this type of role. As a personal mission, I strive to empower and improve other's outlooks and circumstances. I believe that being genuine and nurturing, along with professional and driven, is an essential", "tags": [{"Email": "18041997sh@gmail.com", "start_pos": 23, "end_pos": 43, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "18041997sh@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SOURABH SHARMA", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 14, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SOURABH SHARMA"}, {"Phone": "18041997sh@gmail.com", "start_pos": 23, "end_pos": 43, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "18041997sh@gmail.com"}, {"DATE": "August 26, 2020", "start_pos": 44, "end_pos": 59, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "August 26, 2020"}, {"Designation": "Android Application Developer,", "start_pos": 64, "end_pos": 94, "tag": "Designation", "type": "Designation", "text": "Android Application Developer,"}, {"ORG": "Excellence Technosoft Private Limited", "start_pos": 161, "end_pos": 198, "tag": "ORG", "type": "ORG", "text": "Excellence Technosoft Private Limited"}, {"Designation": "Android Application Developer.", "start_pos": 224, "end_pos": 254, "tag": "Designation", "type": "Designation", "text": "Android Application Developer."}, {"ExperianceYears": "several years", "start_pos": 259, "end_pos": 272, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "type": "ExperianceYears", "text": "several years"}]}
{"line": "PRIYA KUMARI  Moh- Bada Bazar Amroha Contact No: - 7902056638 Distt- Amroha (U.P.)- 244221 Email- pt135489@gmail.com : Gender Marital Status : Date of Birth Nationality Language Marital Shri Lal Mohan Thakur 13/05/1999 Indian English & Hindi Female Unmarried PERSONAL STRENGTHS:- Hard Working, Confidence , Puntuality DECLARATION:- I hereby declare that all the information are provided above is true to the bestof my knowledge. (PRIYA KUMARI)", "tags": [{"Email": "pt135489@gmail.com", "start_pos": 98, "end_pos": 116, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "pt135489@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "PRIYA KUMARI", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "PRIYA KUMARI"}, {"Phone": "7902056638", "start_pos": 50, "end_pos": 60, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "7902056638"}, {"Phone": "pt135489@gmail.com", "start_pos": 97, "end_pos": 115, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "pt135489@gmail.com"}, {"DOB": "13/05/1999", "start_pos": 207, "end_pos": 217, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "13/05/1999"}, {"PERSON": "(PRIYA KUMARI)", "start_pos": 428, "end_pos": 442, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "(PRIYA KUMARI)"}]}
{"line": "B.E., Computer Science Engineering E-mail:-mehtadeepali2012@gmail.com DEEPALI MEHTA Mobile no: 9993521532  Gwalior", "tags": [{"Email": "-mehtadeepali2012@gmail.com", "start_pos": 42, "end_pos": 69, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-mehtadeepali2012@gmail.com"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.E., Computer Science Engineering", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 34, "tag": "EducationDegree", "type": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.E., Computer Science Engineering"}, {"PERSON": "DEEPALI MEHTA", "start_pos": 70, "end_pos": 83, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "DEEPALI MEHTA"}, {"Phone": "9993521532", "start_pos": 95, "end_pos": 105, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9993521532"}]}
{"line": "InternInternB.Tech/B.E.B.Tech/B.E.Computer Science & EngineeringBengal College of Engineering andTechnology | 2019CGPA - 6.69/10.00XIIXIIHoly Mission Secondary School, Patna| 2014Percentage - 61.00%XXHoly Mission Secondary School, Patna| 2012CGPA - 8.80/10.00SUMMARYSUMMARYDetail-oriented and motivated Computer Science and EngineeringComputer Science and EngineeringFresher Fresher offering a basic knowledge of designing, developing and testing softwaresolution. Possesses familiarity with programming languages - C, Core Java, C, Core Java, and PHPPHPand other software engineering activities such as integration testing, algorithm & dataanalysis, software troubleshooting, and preparing documentation. Demonstrates goodcommunication skills and the ability to work in a collaborative, team environment.PROFESSIONAL DETAILSPROFESSIONAL DETAILSNaresh IT, HyderabdadNaresh IT, HyderabdadWorked on Project titled: Route Suggestion SystemProject titled: Route Suggestion SystemDescription:Description:The Route Suggestion System is a web based system which would enable usersto choose the shortest route from one location to another location using a greedyalgorithm. In this project travelers may choose the best route to choose. There are twotypes of user which is admin and travelers. Travelers can only check the shortest route.ACADEMIC DETAILSACADEMIC DETAILSCERTIFICATESCERTIFICATESCore JavaCore JavaDATE OF BIRTHDATE OF BIRTHFebruary 5, 1998SKILLSSKILLSFrameworkFrameworkAngular JSProgramming LanguagesProgramming LanguagesC PHP Core JavaAREAS OF INTERESTSAREAS OF INTERESTSCore JavaCore JavaMathematicsMathematicsLanguageLanguageEnglishHindiPERSONALITY TRAITSPERSONALITY TRAITSCritical ThinkingDecision MakingProblem SolvingAnalytical SkillsTime ManagementHobbiesHobbiesPlaying CricketPrince KumarNew Sabajpura, P.O. Khagaul, Patna, Bihar - 801105+91-7797722177 princekumar77977@gmail.com InternInternB.Tech/B.E.B.Tech/B.E.Computer Science & EngineeringBengal College of Engineering andTechnology | 2019CGPA - 6.69/10.00XIIXIIHoly Mission Secondary School, Patna| 2014Percentage - 61.00%XXHoly Mission Secondary School, Patna| 2012CGPA - 8.80/10.00SUMMARYSUMMARYDetail-oriented and motivated Computer Science and EngineeringComputer Science and EngineeringFresher Fresher offering a basic knowledge of designing, developing and testing softwaresolution. Possesses familiarity with programming languages - C, Core Java, C, Core Java, and PHPPHPand other software engineering activities such as integration testing, algorithm & dataanalysis, software troubleshooting, and preparing documentation. Demonstrates goodcommunication skills and the ability to work in a collaborative, team environment.PROFESSIONAL DETAILSPROFESSIONAL DETAILSNaresh IT, HyderabdadNaresh IT, HyderabdadWorked on Project titled: Route Suggestion SystemProject titled: Route Suggestion SystemDescription:Description:The Route Suggestion System is a web based system which would enable usersto choose the shortest route from one location to another location using a greedyalgorithm. In this project travelers may choose the best route to choose. There are twotypes of user which is admin and travelers. Travelers can only check the shortest route.ACADEMIC DETAILSACADEMIC DETAILSCERTIFICATESCERTIFICATESCore JavaCore JavaDATE OF BIRTHDATE OF BIRTHFebruary 5, 1998SKILLSSKILLSFrameworkFrameworkAngular JSProgramming LanguagesProgramming LanguagesC PHP Core JavaAREAS OF INTERESTSAREAS OF INTERESTSCore JavaCore JavaMathematicsMathematicsLanguageLanguageEnglishHindiPERSONALITY TRAITSPERSONALITY TRAITSCritical ThinkingDecision MakingProblem SolvingAnalytical SkillsTime ManagementHobbiesHobbiesPlaying CricketPrince KumarNew Sabajpura, P.O. Khagaul, Patna, Bihar - 801105+91-7797722177 princekumar77977@gmail.com", "tags": [{"Email": "princekumar77977@gmail.com", "start_pos": 3761, "end_pos": 3787, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "princekumar77977@gmail.com"}, {"ORG": "EngineeringBengal College of Engineering andTechnology", "start_pos": 53, "end_pos": 107, "tag": "ORG", "type": "ORG", "text": "EngineeringBengal College of Engineering andTechnology"}, {"DATE": "2019CGPA", "start_pos": 110, "end_pos": 118, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "2019CGPA"}, {"CARDINAL": "6.69/10.00XIIXIIHoly", "start_pos": 121, "end_pos": 141, "tag": "CARDINAL", "type": "CARDINAL", "text": "6.69/10.00XIIXIIHoly"}, {"DATE": "2014Percentage", "start_pos": 175, "end_pos": 189, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "2014Percentage"}, {"CARDINAL": "61.00%XXHoly", "start_pos": 192, "end_pos": 204, "tag": "CARDINAL", "type": "CARDINAL", "text": "61.00%XXHoly"}, {"DATE": "2012CGPA", "start_pos": 238, "end_pos": 246, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "2012CGPA"}, {"CARDINAL": "8.80/10.00SUMMARYSUMMARYDetail-oriented", "start_pos": 249, "end_pos": 288, "tag": "CARDINAL", "type": "CARDINAL", "text": "8.80/10.00SUMMARYSUMMARYDetail-oriented"}, {"CARDINAL": "are", "start_pos": 3128, "end_pos": 3131, "tag": "CARDINAL", "type": "CARDINAL", "text": "are"}]}
{"line": "BIMALABATI MUNDA Objective: seek the challenging in and me and fast environment, my knowledge and with ✉mbimalabati93@gmail.com ☎ +91- 7205960499 To seek the challenging position in Software industry that needs innovation, creativity, dedication and enable me to continue to work in a challenging and fast paced environment, leveraging my current knowledge and fostering creativity with many learning opportunities.  Good in developing web applications using Angular8 as a frontend web designing framework and basic knowledge on Sql server,Mongodb and Mysql database.  Good knowledge in MySQL Server and UI Development Technologies by developing Single Page Application (SPA) using Angular8, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3 etc.  Strong communication, collaboration & team building skills with proficiency at grasping new technical concepts & utilize the same in a productive manner.  Have good knowledge on consuming REST API’s.  Having good working knowledge on Angular8 Framework concepts like Routing, Directives, Services.  Having good experience on writing SQL queries, stored procedures or accessing backend.  Hands on experience and knowledge in Single Page Application Development using Angular8. Technical Skills:  Operating System  Server side Technologies  Client Side Technologies  Web Technologies  IDE’s  Database", "tags": [{"Email": "mbimalabati93@gmail.com", "start_pos": 104, "end_pos": 127, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "mbimalabati93@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "BIMALABATI MUNDA", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 16, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "BIMALABATI MUNDA"}, {"Phone": "+91- 7205960499", "start_pos": 130, "end_pos": 145, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91- 7205960499"}]}
{"line": "SOWMHITHRA MOHANRAJ GRADUATED IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY E-MAIL:Sowmhithra.it15@bitsathy.ac.in ADDRESS: 6B/1,Sri Sabari Illam,Anjaneya Nagar Gobichettipalayam-638452 CONTACT: 9629114658 OBJECTIVE", "tags": [{"Email": "Sowmhithra.it15@bitsathy.ac.in", "start_pos": 63, "end_pos": 93, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Sowmhithra.it15@bitsathy.ac.in"}, {"PERSON": "SOWMHITHRA MOHANRAJ", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 19, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SOWMHITHRA MOHANRAJ"}, {"Phone": "9629114658", "start_pos": 174, "end_pos": 184, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9629114658"}]}
{"line": "MANVI Contact no: +91-7452928617 Email:manvikh95@gmail.com  Father Name Chachra Date Sepr 1995 English opp. road, Najibabad Date of Birth Signature", "tags": [{"Email": "manvikh95@gmail.com", "start_pos": 39, "end_pos": 58, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "manvikh95@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "MANVI", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 5, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "MANVI"}, {"Phone": "+91-7452928617", "start_pos": 18, "end_pos": 32, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-7452928617"}, {"DOB": "Sepr 1995", "start_pos": 84, "end_pos": 93, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "Sepr 1995"}]}
{"line": "Shinde Pradeep Sukhadev Mob No:9860583903 Gmail:pradeepshinde0204@gmail.com  Name Languages Date of Nationality : Indian. Declaration: Pradeep Shinde I hereby declare that the above written particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and belief. Thanking you Place:Pandharpur Date:10 Aug 2020", "tags": [{"Email": "pradeepshinde0204@gmail.com", "start_pos": 48, "end_pos": 75, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "pradeepshinde0204@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Shinde Pradeep Sukhadev", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 23, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Shinde Pradeep Sukhadev"}, {"DATE": "Aug 2020", "start_pos": 288, "end_pos": 296, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "Aug 2020"}]}
{"line": "Mahender sharma Email:sharma27july1999@gmail.com Mobile : +919540354422 CURRICULUM VITAE of sharma : chhagan lal sharma I hereby declare that the above information given by me is true to the best of my knowledge and belief. DECLARATION", "tags": [{"Email": "sharma27july1999@gmail.com", "start_pos": 22, "end_pos": 48, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "sharma27july1999@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Mahender sharma", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 15, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Mahender sharma"}, {"Phone": "+919540354422", "start_pos": 58, "end_pos": 71, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+919540354422"}]}
{"line": "CURRICULUM VITAE Guriya kumari Tower 3, Flat no-108, Xaviers urbtech 168 Mobile:07001499226 Email:guriyapragati97@gmail.com Personal Information  Date of Birth 04 February 1998 Mr. Pramod kumar Thakur Female Single Hindi, English Father’s Name Sex Marital Status Language Known Date March 2020", "tags": [{"Email": "guriyapragati97@gmail.com", "start_pos": 98, "end_pos": 123, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "guriyapragati97@gmail.com"}, {"DOB": "04 February 1998", "start_pos": 159, "end_pos": 175, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "04 February 1998"}, {"DATE": "March 2020", "start_pos": 282, "end_pos": 292, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "March 2020"}]}
{"line": "CIRRICULUM VITAE Name:PreeteeKailasRautray Mobile:-8698815334 Email:-rautraypriti@gmail.com Specialization Science Science Distinction Science Distinction Commerceand Science,Pune College, shirur", "tags": [{"Email": "-rautraypriti@gmail.com", "start_pos": 68, "end_pos": 91, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-rautraypriti@gmail.com"}]}
{"line": "Name:Riya Kukreti Address :Vill-Bhauwala,P/O-Bhauwala,Dehradun,Uttarakhand Pin Code :248007 Mobile :9758142676 Email :kukretiriya65@gmail.com Declaration Place: Dehradun Date: 30/January/2020 (Riya Kukreti)", "tags": [{"Email": "kukretiriya65@gmail.com", "start_pos": 118, "end_pos": 141, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "kukretiriya65@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Kukreti", "start_pos": 10, "end_pos": 17, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Kukreti"}, {"GPE": "Dehradun", "start_pos": 161, "end_pos": 169, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Dehradun"}, {"DOB": "30/January/2020", "start_pos": 176, "end_pos": 191, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "30/January/2020"}, {"PERSON": "(Riya Kukreti)", "start_pos": 192, "end_pos": 206, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "(Riya Kukreti)"}]}
{"line": "Phone:- +91-8901023941 Email Id:-paankajy@gmail.com Pankaj Yadav Primary Skills:-JAVA/JEE Personal Details:-  Date of Birth: 12-June-1990 Current Location: Delhi/NCR Permanent Address: Rewari, Haryana", "tags": [{"Email": "-paankajy@gmail.com", "start_pos": 32, "end_pos": 51, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-paankajy@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "+91-8901023941", "start_pos": 8, "end_pos": 22, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-8901023941"}, {"PERSON": "Pankaj Yadav", "start_pos": 52, "end_pos": 64, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Pankaj Yadav"}, {"DOB": "12-June-1990", "start_pos": 124, "end_pos": 136, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "12-June-1990"}, {"GPE": "Rewari, Haryana", "start_pos": 184, "end_pos": 199, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Rewari, Haryana"}]}
{"line": "RESUME Ankit Singh Home No.-669 New Harbansh Nagar, Ghaziabad-201001(up) Contact No. –7544944070 E-mail :-ankit_4t7@yahoo.com  Kumar Singh Fathers name Late Subash Maya Devi 16-01-1999 Male Marital status- Language & English Nationality Indian hereby declare the information provided above is true to my knowledge. Palace Date", "tags": [{"Email": "-ankit_4t7@yahoo.com", "start_pos": 105, "end_pos": 125, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-ankit_4t7@yahoo.com"}, {"PERSON": "Ankit Singh", "start_pos": 7, "end_pos": 18, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Ankit Singh"}, {"Phone": "–7544944070", "start_pos": 85, "end_pos": 96, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "–7544944070"}, {"PERSON": "Kumar Singh", "start_pos": 126, "end_pos": 137, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Kumar Singh"}, {"DOB": "16-01-1999", "start_pos": 173, "end_pos": 183, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "16-01-1999"}]}
{"line": "SHAIKH SIDDIQ Mobile:9839291148 Email:sid370578@gmail.com Address:vill-Uttrai,post-Maryadpur,dist-Mau,221602 PERSONAL INFORMATION . Name: Shaikh Siddiq .Date of birth:06-06-1998", "tags": [{"Email": "sid370578@gmail.com", "start_pos": 38, "end_pos": 57, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "sid370578@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SHAIKH SIDDIQ", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 13, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SHAIKH SIDDIQ"}, {"PERSON": "Shaikh Siddiq", "start_pos": 138, "end_pos": 151, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Shaikh Siddiq"}]}
{"line": "RESUME Deepali Kumari Gupta Nagar an where my my Mobile :8826658400 E-mail :guptadeepali904@gmail.com Address H-10/6,Second Floor Malviya Nagar New Delhi (110017) Objective  Fathers Female 25 Languages Blhar Pin", "tags": [{"Email": "guptadeepali904@gmail.com", "start_pos": 76, "end_pos": 101, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "guptadeepali904@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Deepali Kumari Gupta", "start_pos": 7, "end_pos": 27, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Deepali Kumari Gupta"}, {"GPE": "Malviya Nagar New Delhi", "start_pos": 130, "end_pos": 153, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Malviya Nagar New Delhi"}]}
{"line": "SACHIN KUMAR H.No- 7, GALI NO- 6, Saraswati colony, Sehatpur, Faridabad, Haryana-121003 Mob- +91-7303011735 Email Id:-Sk31817@gmail.com EXPERIENCE •", "tags": [{"Email": "-Sk31817@gmail.com", "start_pos": 117, "end_pos": 135, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-Sk31817@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SACHIN KUMAR", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SACHIN KUMAR"}, {"GPE": "Sehatpur, Faridabad, Haryana-121003", "start_pos": 52, "end_pos": 87, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Sehatpur, Faridabad, Haryana-121003"}, {"Phone": "+91-7303011735", "start_pos": 93, "end_pos": 107, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-7303011735"}]}
{"line": "SHIVEK KUMAR SINGH Email Id :siveksinghrajput@gmail.com Phone NO:-7549995983", "tags": [{"Email": "siveksinghrajput@gmail.com", "start_pos": 29, "end_pos": 55, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "siveksinghrajput@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SHIVEK KUMAR SINGH", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 18, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SHIVEK KUMAR SINGH"}, {"Phone": ":siveksinghrajput@gmail.com", "start_pos": 28, "end_pos": 55, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": ":siveksinghrajput@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "NO:-7549995983", "start_pos": 62, "end_pos": 76, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "NO:-7549995983"}]}
{"line": "RESUME ANSHU KUMARI SUMAN Graduate (B.Tech :Computer Science) Accurate Institute of Management and Technology, Delhi MOBILE : +917840885508 EMAIL ID:anshuminapur@gmail.com PERSONAL DETAILS  Father’s Name Permanent Name Sex Contact No. Languages Known Shashi Ranjan Kumar 05 Jan 1998 Female Single : Indian : : : : : : : +917840885508 : Muzaffarpur, Bihar DOB Martial Status Nationality", "tags": [{"Email": "anshuminapur@gmail.com", "start_pos": 149, "end_pos": 171, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "anshuminapur@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "ANSHU KUMARI SUMAN", "start_pos": 7, "end_pos": 25, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "ANSHU KUMARI SUMAN"}, {"ORG": "Accurate Institute of Management and Technology,", "start_pos": 62, "end_pos": 110, "tag": "ORG", "type": "ORG", "text": "Accurate Institute of Management and Technology,"}, {"GPE": "Delhi", "start_pos": 111, "end_pos": 116, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Delhi"}, {"Phone": "+917840885508", "start_pos": 126, "end_pos": 139, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+917840885508"}, {"DOB": "05 Jan 1998", "start_pos": 270, "end_pos": 281, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "05 Jan 1998"}, {"Phone": "+917840885508", "start_pos": 319, "end_pos": 332, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+917840885508"}, {"GPE": "Muzaffarpur, Bihar", "start_pos": 335, "end_pos": 353, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Muzaffarpur, Bihar"}]}
{"line": "Shahrukh Khan Chowk, Greater Noida ‘Academic Background C-580 NRI CITY PARI Chowk, Greater Noida 8448665526 sk0450230@gmail.com College/School University/Board", "tags": [{"Email": "sk0450230@gmail.com", "start_pos": 108, "end_pos": 127, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "sk0450230@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Shahrukh Khan Chowk,", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 20, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Shahrukh Khan Chowk,"}, {"GPE": "Greater Noida", "start_pos": 21, "end_pos": 34, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Greater Noida"}, {"GPE": "Greater Noida", "start_pos": 83, "end_pos": 96, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Greater Noida"}, {"Phone": "8448665526 sk0450230@gmail.com", "start_pos": 97, "end_pos": 127, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "8448665526 sk0450230@gmail.com"}]}
{"line": "SHIRISH POKHREL Noida, 9899338995|pokharelshirish@gmail.com Noida, U.P.", "tags": [{"Email": "pokharelshirish@gmail.com", "start_pos": 34, "end_pos": 59, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "pokharelshirish@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SHIRISH POKHREL", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 15, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SHIRISH POKHREL"}, {"GPE": "Noida,", "start_pos": 16, "end_pos": 22, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Noida,"}, {"Phone": "9899338995|pokharelshirish@gmail.com", "start_pos": 23, "end_pos": 59, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9899338995|pokharelshirish@gmail.com"}, {"GPE": "Noida, U.P.", "start_pos": 60, "end_pos": 71, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Noida, U.P."}]}
{"line": "CURICULUM VITAE E-Mail:atulyarai7897@gmail.com Mobile:+91-9608370771 AtulyaKumari Fresheryears;Edu:BCA Objective:-  :Feb.11th1995  Father’sName :Sh.SatyaPrakash Page-1-  MaritalStatus :Married Itisherebydeclarethattheabovefurnisheddetailsaretruewithprovenrecords.Therefore,Iseeka suitableplacementcommensuratewithmyqualificationandexperience. [Noida] Declaration:- Atulyakumari . Page-2-of2", "tags": [{"Email": "atulyarai7897@gmail.com", "start_pos": 23, "end_pos": 46, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "atulyarai7897@gmail.com"}]}
{"line": "RESUME PRAVEENA K E BLOCK HOUSE NO 386 SHAKURPUR mobile no: 9971377309 DELHI-110034 Email:praveenakswamy93@gmail.com PERSONAL PROFILE:   DATE OF BIRTH : 15.12.1993  GENDER : FEMALE  NATIONALITY : HINDU  FATHER NAME : K KANDASWAMY  LANGUAGE KNOWN : TAMIL,ENGLISH AND HINDI", "tags": [{"Email": "praveenakswamy93@gmail.com", "start_pos": 90, "end_pos": 116, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "praveenakswamy93@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "PRAVEENA K", "start_pos": 7, "end_pos": 17, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "PRAVEENA K"}, {"Phone": "9971377309", "start_pos": 60, "end_pos": 70, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9971377309"}, {"DOB": "15.12.1993", "start_pos": 153, "end_pos": 163, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "15.12.1993"}]}
{"line": "Laravel Developer – Rahul Chaudhari. Email:chaudharirahul718@gmail.com Mobile: +91-9326644143 Personal Details:  Date of Birth: 15th Dec 1996 Declaration: Location: Pune Marital Status: Single Permanent Address:Gulmohor Apt. Near kothrud Stand Kothrud Pune:-411038 Language known: English,Marathi, Hindi", "tags": [{"Email": "chaudharirahul718@gmail.com", "start_pos": 43, "end_pos": 70, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "chaudharirahul718@gmail.com"}, {"Designation": "Laravel Developer", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 17, "tag": "Designation", "type": "Designation", "text": "Laravel Developer"}, {"PERSON": "Rahul Chaudhari.", "start_pos": 20, "end_pos": 36, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Rahul Chaudhari."}, {"Phone": "+91-9326644143", "start_pos": 79, "end_pos": 93, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-9326644143"}, {"DOB": "15th Dec 1996", "start_pos": 127, "end_pos": 140, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "15th Dec 1996"}, {"GPE": "Pune", "start_pos": 164, "end_pos": 168, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Pune"}]}
{"line": "Gautam kumar Address : Rz-305/m raj nagar part 2 palam colony 110077 new delhi Phone: +91 9958310469 Email :Gautam.kumar09874@gmail.com", "tags": [{"Email": "Gautam.kumar09874@gmail.com", "start_pos": 108, "end_pos": 135, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Gautam.kumar09874@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Gautam kumar", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Gautam kumar"}, {"GPE": "new delhi", "start_pos": 69, "end_pos": 78, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "new delhi"}, {"Phone": "9958310469", "start_pos": 90, "end_pos": 100, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9958310469"}]}
{"line": "Contact no:9783525155 Rajat Jain Contact no:9783525155 Rajat Jain Email:rajatjain9994@gmail.com Job Objective:", "tags": [{"Email": "rajatjain9994@gmail.com", "start_pos": 72, "end_pos": 95, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "rajatjain9994@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "no:9783525155", "start_pos": 8, "end_pos": 21, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "no:9783525155"}, {"PERSON": "Rajat Jain", "start_pos": 22, "end_pos": 32, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Rajat Jain"}, {"PERSON": "Rajat Jain", "start_pos": 55, "end_pos": 65, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Rajat Jain"}]}
{"line": "CURRICULUM VITAE DHIRAJ KUMAR Address: E-36, 2ND FLOOR, BUDHNAGAR, INDERPURI NEW DELHI, -110012 Phone: 9540470745 E-mail:dhirajkumar09526@gmail.com Date of Birth: 26/04/1995", "tags": [{"Email": "dhirajkumar09526@gmail.com", "start_pos": 121, "end_pos": 147, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "dhirajkumar09526@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "DHIRAJ KUMAR", "start_pos": 17, "end_pos": 29, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "DHIRAJ KUMAR"}, {"GPE": "BUDHNAGAR, INDERPURI NEW DELHI,", "start_pos": 56, "end_pos": 87, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "BUDHNAGAR, INDERPURI NEW DELHI,"}, {"Phone": "9540470745", "start_pos": 103, "end_pos": 113, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9540470745"}, {"DOB": "26/04/1995", "start_pos": 163, "end_pos": 173, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "26/04/1995"}]}
{"line": "College Projects  Small Search Engine (The Search Engine is developed in php. It works look like as Google to Search the thinks using Keywords)  GST Calculator (The GST Calculator developed in C programming. It calculate the all GST slab rate like (18%, 5%, 12%)  School Management System. (The School Management System is web Application Developed In Java Server Page (JSP) It work to maintain the Student Record.)  Desktop Assistant (The Desktop Assistant is developed in Python.it works on voice Recognition technology and performs operations like .play music, open browser and Search user query on Google.) SHUBHAM SAINI Mobile: 8650539007 Email:Shub10845@gmail.com Ghaushala Road Shamli 247776(U.P)", "tags": [{"Email": "Shub10845@gmail.com", "start_pos": 654, "end_pos": 673, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "Shub10845@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SHUBHAM SAINI", "start_pos": 615, "end_pos": 628, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SHUBHAM SAINI"}, {"Phone": "8650539007", "start_pos": 637, "end_pos": 647, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "8650539007"}]}
{"line": "CURRICULUM VITA PostAppliedfor : : Post for NAME No. Email SHIVAM ~ Phulpur Prayagraj Uttar Pradesh 212402, mechanicalEngineeringworks SHIVAM TIWARI Address MobileNo. EmailId : : Vill+Post–Pratappur,PhulpurPrayagraj(Allahabad) UttarPradesh212402. +91-7309780801 :shivamtiwariengineer@gmail.com", "tags": [{"Email": "shivamtiwariengineer@gmail.com", "start_pos": 263, "end_pos": 293, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "shivamtiwariengineer@gmail.com"}, {"GPE": "Uttar Pradesh", "start_pos": 86, "end_pos": 99, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Uttar Pradesh"}, {"PERSON": "SHIVAM TIWARI", "start_pos": 135, "end_pos": 148, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SHIVAM TIWARI"}, {"Phone": "+91-7309780801", "start_pos": 247, "end_pos": 261, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-7309780801"}]}
{"line": "Rishabh B.tech (computer science and engineering) Contact: - 8826839715, 7015747826 E-mail:-khokherrishabh1997@gmail.com PRESENT ADDRESS:- Gali No.3, Near Pooja Medical Store, Vill. Challera, Sector 44 Noida, Uttar Pradesh CAREER OBJECTIVE:- INTERPERSONAL SKILL & STRENGTHS:- PERSONAL DETAILS:- PERSONAL DETAILS:- INTERPERSONAL SKILL & STRENGTHS:-  Ability to rapidly build relationship and set up trust.  Ability to cope up with different situations.  Team work Spirit  Flexible  Quick Learner  Leadership Quality FATHER’S NAME: - Yoginder DATE OF BIRTH: - October ADDRESS: Shiv Colony, Ward no. 5, 122103 LANGUAGE KNOWN: - Hindi, and NATIONALITY: - Indian - Playing Kabaddi, Wrestling & Cricket INTEREST AND Gardening, watching movies DECLARATION:-  I do hereby declare that above information is true to the best of my knowledge. Place:- Date:- Signature", "tags": [{"Email": "-khokherrishabh1997@gmail.com", "start_pos": 91, "end_pos": 120, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-khokherrishabh1997@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Rishabh", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 7, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Rishabh"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.tech", "start_pos": 8, "end_pos": 14, "tag": "EducationDegree", "type": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.tech"}, {"Phone": "8826839715, 7015747826", "start_pos": 61, "end_pos": 83, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "8826839715, 7015747826"}, {"GPE": "Noida, Uttar Pradesh", "start_pos": 202, "end_pos": 222, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Noida, Uttar Pradesh"}]}
{"line": "BHANWAR LAL SAINI Correspondence Address: Jaisinghpura khor,Jaipur, Rajasthan. Mobile:+91-7976492130 E-mail:bhanwar345@gmail.com  • Competitive Programming(6monts)on Geeks and CodeChef. PERSONAL DETAILS:- • Date of Birth:- 02-july-1994 • Languages Known:- English Hindi • Nationality:- Indian", "tags": [{"Email": "bhanwar345@gmail.com", "start_pos": 108, "end_pos": 128, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "bhanwar345@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "BHANWAR LAL SAINI", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 17, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "BHANWAR LAL SAINI"}, {"DOB": "02-july-1994", "start_pos": 222, "end_pos": 234, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "02-july-1994"}]}
{"line": "SHIVAM ARYA Phone:+91.8966064885, 74156602 Email:aryashivam836@gmail.com Address: Mahaveerpura Ward no 1 Sector 8 Gurgoan(H.R)", "tags": [{"Email": "aryashivam836@gmail.com", "start_pos": 49, "end_pos": 72, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "aryashivam836@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SHIVAM ARYA", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 11, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SHIVAM ARYA"}, {"Phone": "74156602", "start_pos": 34, "end_pos": 42, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "74156602"}]}
{"line": "AAYUSH MISRA Contact No . +91-9565911911 DOB : Aug 20 ,1994 , Varanasi misraaayush94@gmail.com CAREER OBJECTIVE", "tags": [{"Email": "misraaayush94@gmail.com", "start_pos": 71, "end_pos": 94, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "misraaayush94@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "AAYUSH MISRA", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "AAYUSH MISRA"}, {"Phone": "+91-9565911911", "start_pos": 26, "end_pos": 40, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-9565911911"}, {"DOB": "Aug 20 ,1994", "start_pos": 47, "end_pos": 59, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "Aug 20 ,1994"}, {"GPE": "Varanasi", "start_pos": 62, "end_pos": 70, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Varanasi"}]}
{"line": "Puneet Prajapati H No. 1534 , Dwarka nagar Coach fectory road bhopal Mo. No. 7905726899 Email :xtranet.puneet@gmail.com Personal Details: Father’s Name - Mr. Rajesh Prajapati Mother’s Name - Mrs. Shivkanti Devi Date of Birth - 13- 03 - 1997 Nationality - Indian Marital Status - Unmarried", "tags": [{"Email": "xtranet.puneet@gmail.com", "start_pos": 95, "end_pos": 119, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "xtranet.puneet@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Puneet Prajapati", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 16, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Puneet Prajapati"}, {"GPE": "Dwarka nagar Coach fectory road bhopal", "start_pos": 30, "end_pos": 68, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Dwarka nagar Coach fectory road bhopal"}, {"Phone": "7905726899", "start_pos": 77, "end_pos": 87, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "7905726899"}, {"DOB": "13- 03 - 1997", "start_pos": 227, "end_pos": 240, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "13- 03 - 1997"}]}
{"line": "RITU CHAUHAN E-mail:chauhanritu50@gmail.com Contact No:+91-8076580295 Address: 168 block-3 type-2 Mir Dard Lane M.A.M.C Campus, Delhi-110002 CAREER OBJECTIVE:", "tags": [{"Email": "chauhanritu50@gmail.com", "start_pos": 20, "end_pos": 43, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "chauhanritu50@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "RITU CHAUHAN", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 12, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "RITU CHAUHAN"}]}
{"line": "CURRICULUM VITAE AMIT YADAV  Pradesh E-mail:amit971996@gmail.com MOBILE NO. :+918090343678 PERSONAL DETAILS PERSONAL DETAILS Father’s Name : Mr. Ram Achal Yadav  Date of Birth :10-07-1996   Mother’s Name : Mrs. Gayatri Devi  Nationality : Indian  Languages Known : Hindi, English", "tags": [{"Email": "amit971996@gmail.com", "start_pos": 44, "end_pos": 64, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "amit971996@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "AMIT YADAV", "start_pos": 17, "end_pos": 27, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "AMIT YADAV"}, {"Phone": ":+918090343678", "start_pos": 75, "end_pos": 89, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": ":+918090343678"}]}
{"line": "Swati Srivastava E-mail:swatisrivastava0417@gmail.com Contact No: +91-8766244405 2016 2014 OBJECTIVE Personal Details:  Father’s Name October 17, 1998. Languages known Hobbies Address Reading, Listening music. Triveni Nagar, LUCKNOW. Mr. RK Srivastava Date of Birth Hindi and English. www.cv-resumesamples.blogspot.com / www.resumemonster.in", "tags": [{"Email": "swatisrivastava0417@gmail.com", "start_pos": 24, "end_pos": 53, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "swatisrivastava0417@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Swati Srivastava", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 16, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Swati Srivastava"}, {"Phone": "+91-8766244405", "start_pos": 66, "end_pos": 80, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-8766244405"}, {"DATE": "2016 2014", "start_pos": 81, "end_pos": 90, "tag": "DATE", "type": "DATE", "text": "2016 2014"}, {"DOB": "October 17, 1998.", "start_pos": 133, "end_pos": 150, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "October 17, 1998."}]}
{"line": "MANO SAI CHANDU PEDAVALLI Email:manochandu6@gmail.com SOFTWARE JAVA DEVELOPER Mobile: +91-9154402246", "tags": [{"Email": "manochandu6@gmail.com", "start_pos": 32, "end_pos": 53, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "manochandu6@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "MANO SAI CHANDU PEDAVALLI", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 25, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "MANO SAI CHANDU PEDAVALLI"}, {"Phone": "+91-9154402246", "start_pos": 86, "end_pos": 100, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+91-9154402246"}]}
{"line": "Curriculum Vitae Name: SUKANYA CHAUHAN Contact No:+91-9953623916 Email:chauhanabi98@gmail.com OBJECTIVE:", "tags": [{"Email": "chauhanabi98@gmail.com", "start_pos": 71, "end_pos": 93, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "chauhanabi98@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SUKANYA CHAUHAN", "start_pos": 23, "end_pos": 38, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SUKANYA CHAUHAN"}]}
{"line": "DIVYA SAXENA SRIVASTAVA Address: F-101, Mobile No:-+919810127385 Sampad Prime, Email ID:-divyasaxena214@gmail.com near Sargasan Cross Road, Gandhinagar, Gujarat (382009) PERSONAL DETAILS  Date of Birth :  Husband Name : Mr. Sanidhya Srivastava  Nationality : Indian  Languages Known : Hindi & English 14th MAR, 1995 Declaration: I hereby declare that the above mentioned statements are true and correct to the best of my knowledge and good faith. Place: GANDHINAGAR (DIVYA)", "tags": [{"Email": "-divyasaxena214@gmail.com", "start_pos": 88, "end_pos": 113, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-divyasaxena214@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "DIVYA SAXENA SRIVASTAVA", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 23, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "DIVYA SAXENA SRIVASTAVA"}, {"GPE": "Gandhinagar, Gujarat", "start_pos": 140, "end_pos": 160, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "Gandhinagar, Gujarat"}, {"DOB": "14th MAR, 1995", "start_pos": 305, "end_pos": 319, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "14th MAR, 1995"}]}
{"line": "SAMEEKSHA SHARMA B.TECH 4th Year (CS) Mobile no: +91 9953715845; Email Id:sameekshasharma497@gmail.com", "tags": [{"Email": "sameekshasharma497@gmail.com", "start_pos": 74, "end_pos": 102, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "sameekshasharma497@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "SAMEEKSHA SHARMA", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 16, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "SAMEEKSHA SHARMA"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.TECH", "start_pos": 17, "end_pos": 23, "tag": "EducationDegree", "type": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.TECH"}, {"Phone": "9953715845;", "start_pos": 53, "end_pos": 64, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "9953715845;"}]}
{"line": "Dave Mobile Number:-+917737651038 Job Objective Email:khushaldave2@gmail.com Personal information  Mr. Madhusudan Dave Date of Birth Father’s name Permanent Address : : : 10 September 1992 Pin Code-342001 P. No. – 494, 4/5thB road, Sardarpura Jodhpur. I hereby declare that particulars given here are true and complete to the best of my knowledge and belief. (Khushal Dave)", "tags": [{"Email": "khushaldave2@gmail.com", "start_pos": 54, "end_pos": 76, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "khushaldave2@gmail.com"}, {"DOB": "10 September 1992", "start_pos": 170, "end_pos": 187, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "10 September 1992"}, {"PERSON": "(Khushal Dave)", "start_pos": 358, "end_pos": 372, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "(Khushal Dave)"}]}
{"line": "CURRICULUM VITAE JYOTI GOSWAMI H.NO.369 Near P.W.D. office Rasal chowk, Jabalpur (M.P )482001 Mob: +9174800147 E-Mail :jyotigoswamisrist@gmail.com Career Objectives:", "tags": [{"Email": "jyotigoswamisrist@gmail.com", "start_pos": 119, "end_pos": 146, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "jyotigoswamisrist@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "JYOTI GOSWAMI", "start_pos": 17, "end_pos": 30, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "JYOTI GOSWAMI"}, {"Phone": "+9174800147", "start_pos": 99, "end_pos": 110, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "+9174800147"}]}
{"line": "Prateek Dwivedi  Contact: - 7683066009,8527386174 B.tech (computer science and engineering) E-mail:-dwivedi.prateek22@gmail.com PERSONAL DETAILS:-  FATHER’S NAME: - ANUPAM DWIVEDI DATE OF BIRTH: - 22nd August 1998 ADDRESS: -811-b Second Floor street no.7 Govindpuri, Kalka Ji, New Delhi, Pin- 110019 LANGUAGE KNOWN: - Hindi and English NATIONALITY: - Indian INTEREST AND HOBBIES: - Playing cricket, chess,snooker, Listening music, watching movies", "tags": [{"Email": "-dwivedi.prateek22@gmail.com", "start_pos": 99, "end_pos": 127, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-dwivedi.prateek22@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Prateek Dwivedi", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 15, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Prateek Dwivedi"}, {"Phone": "7683066009,8527386174", "start_pos": 27, "end_pos": 48, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "7683066009,8527386174"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.tech", "start_pos": 49, "end_pos": 55, "tag": "EducationDegree", "type": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.tech"}, {"PERSON": "ANUPAM DWIVEDI", "start_pos": 163, "end_pos": 177, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "ANUPAM DWIVEDI"}, {"DOB": "22nd August 1998", "start_pos": 195, "end_pos": 211, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "22nd August 1998"}, {"GPE": "New Delhi, Pin-", "start_pos": 275, "end_pos": 290, "tag": "GPE", "type": "GPE", "text": "New Delhi, Pin-"}]}
{"line": "Abhishek Thakur  Contact No: -8580405700,7018924543 B.Tech. Computer Science and Engineering Seeking challenging career in computer science sector to get a position of responsibility, using my skills and efficiency to communicate my ideas and views and commit myself for achieving organization objective with the team effort and my cheerful outlook and performance. Computer Science and Alliance College of Engineering and Design Bangalore We design a healthcare system framework that collects medical data from wireless body area-networks, transmit them through the internet and We developed a web-based application using HTML, CSS and JavaScript, which help the students to ask all the queries about college curriculum. The web-based application takes the quires and replies the queries of the students/user with robotic voice.  C and assembly level C programing.  Android development and XML o NPTEL course of Biology for Engineers and the other Non-Biologist from IIT Madras. o NPTEL course Development Soft Skills and Personality from IIT Kanpur. Email: -abhishek69391@gmail.com Career Objective: Education: Engineering", "tags": [{"Email": "-abhishek69391@gmail.com", "start_pos": 1061, "end_pos": 1085, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "-abhishek69391@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Abhishek Thakur", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 15, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Abhishek Thakur"}, {"Phone": "-8580405700,7018924543", "start_pos": 28, "end_pos": 50, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "-8580405700,7018924543"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.Tech. Computer Science and Engineering", "start_pos": 51, "end_pos": 91, "tag": "EducationDegree", "type": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.Tech. Computer Science and Engineering"}, {"ORG": "Alliance College of Engineering", "start_pos": 386, "end_pos": 417, "tag": "ORG", "type": "ORG", "text": "Alliance College of Engineering"}]}
{"line": "Ambar Chaturvedi E-Mail:ambarchaturvedi01@gmail.com Phone:+91-9650938757 Address:F2-1102GolfCitySector75Noida CAREEROBJECTIVE", "tags": [{"Email": "ambarchaturvedi01@gmail.com", "start_pos": 24, "end_pos": 51, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "ambarchaturvedi01@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Ambar Chaturvedi", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 16, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Ambar Chaturvedi"}]}
{"line": "ASHISH KUMAR RJ-BLOCK,E-32/106, Jai Bharti Camp, East Vinod Nagar, Delhi-110091 Phone:8802251340 Email:ashish.kumar113365@gmail.com growth of the organization.", "tags": [{"Email": "ashish.kumar113365@gmail.com", "start_pos": 103, "end_pos": 131, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "ashish.kumar113365@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "ASHISH KUMAR RJ-BLOCK,E-32/106,", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 31, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "ASHISH KUMAR RJ-BLOCK,E-32/106,"}]}
{"line": "Akshay Kumar[akshaysaini3080@gmail.com] Contact no: +91 -9758023080  Hindi  English PERSONAL DETAILS:  Date of Birth: 11 Sept. 1999  Father’s Name: Mr. Jugpal Singh  Address: VILL- BakarMajra, Nakur, Distr- Saharanpur(U.P) pin:- 247001 Self Appraisal: I have possible of performing well under pressure and under volatility. I have sincerity towards all kinds of work. I am a quick learner, hard worker. I try to find my mistakes & try to turn them from my weaknesses to my strengths. (Akshay Kumar) Page 2 of 2", "tags": [{"Email": "akshaysaini3080@gmail.com", "start_pos": 13, "end_pos": 38, "tag": "Email", "type": "Email", "text": "akshaysaini3080@gmail.com"}, {"PERSON": "Akshay Kumar[akshaysaini3080@gmail.com]", "start_pos": 0, "end_pos": 39, "tag": "PERSON", "type": "PERSON", "text": "Akshay Kumar[akshaysaini3080@gmail.com]"}, {"Phone": "-9758023080", "start_pos": 56, "end_pos": 67, "tag": "Phone", "type": "Phone", "text": "-9758023080"}, {"DOB": "11 Sept. 1999", "start_pos": 121, "end_pos": 134, "tag": "DOB", "type": "DOB", "text": "11 Sept. 1999"}]}
