{"line": "Kapil Choudhary Contact No: +91-9828603355 Email ID: kapilchoudhary086@gmail.com Gurgaon, IN CAREER AIM To work in an environment which is innovative, challenging, rewarding, which offers a profound knowledge base to enhance my talent, exposure and zeal of learning. To work amicably for the betterment of the organization and to take it to new", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Kapil Choudhary", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Kapil Choudhary"}, {"Phone": "+91-9828603355", "start_idx": 28, "tag": "Phone", "text": "+91-9828603355"}, {"Email": "kapilchoudhary086@gmail.com", "start_idx": 53, "tag": "Email", "text": "kapilchoudhary086@gmail.com"}, {"GPE": "Gurgaon, IN", "start_idx": 81, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Gurgaon, IN"}]}
{"line": "heights. PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE KonnectShift ( igital Marketing Executive [ ug 2018-Present", "tags": [{"ORG": "KonnectShift", "start_idx": 378, "tag": "ORG", "text": "KonnectShift"}, {"Designation": "igital Marketing Executive", "start_idx": 393, "tag": "Designation", "text": "igital Marketing Executive"}, {"DATE": "ug 2018-Present", "start_idx": 422, "tag": "DATE", "text": "ug 2018-Present"}]}
{"line": "Managing digital marketing brand campaigns including creative developments, website refreshes and newsletter marketing. Creating engaging social media strategies and execution plans that cultivative audience, increased web presence and enhanced brand awareness. Monitoring the success of Social Media campaigns through Google Analytics, KPI s and Dashboards. Evaluating the effectiveness of marketing programs, provided market analysis and insight to", "tags": []}
{"line": "senior management. Coordinate with Marketing and Sales team as well. Handling day-to-day Search Engine Marketing activities including campaign planning , implementation, budget management, performance review and optimizing paid search campaign. Reports of campaigns with in-depth analysis on the performance of keywords, ad copies, bounce rates etc. Formulating digital strategy for delivering best ROI for campaigns on various result", "tags": []}
{"line": "oriented matrices of cost per click. ROOH-E-JAIPUR (Owner) [July 2018- April 2019]", "tags": [{"ORG": "ROOH-E-JAIPUR", "start_idx": 923, "tag": "ORG", "text": "ROOH-E-JAIPUR"}, {"DATE": "[July 2018- April 2019]", "start_idx": 945, "tag": "DATE", "text": "[July 2018- April 2019]"}]}
{"line": "As the Owner of Rooh-e-Jaipur , I handled multiple roles. Some of those were-", "tags": [{"ORG": "Rooh-e-Jaipur", "start_idx": 16, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Rooh-e-Jaipur"}]}
{"line": "Business Developer As a Business Developer I managed to develop cordial business relations both B2B and B2C .", "tags": [{"Designation": "Business Developer", "start_idx": 78, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Business Developer"}, {"Designation": "Business Developer", "start_idx": 102, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Business Developer"}]}
{"line": "Link Building As the person-in-charge, I fostered the skills of link building and management which I sought important to grow my business.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Social Media Management I realized the importance of maintaining an active online presence for my business, hence I managed the social media accounts for Rooh-e-Jaipur which in turn brought us business.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Influencer Marketing I also understood the significance of influencer marketing. Hence, I had developed professional and cordial relations with influencers like food bloggers which could help to spread the word of mouth marketing for my food outlet.", "tags": []}
{"line": "UnlearnKids [ ept 2015 Feb 2018] Content Development Developed all the Math content for the portal.", "tags": [{"DATE": "ept 2015 Feb 2018]", "start_idx": 794, "tag": "DATE", "text": "ept 2015 Feb 2018]"}]}
{"line": "Developed Highly Personalize Learning Platform using ZPD. . Managed Amazon Web Server.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Reviewed all the uploaded content. Responsible for all the Testings. Business Development", "tags": []}
{"line": "Managed sales pipeline and closing business. Developed a database of qualified leads through referrals, direct mail, email campaigns and networking.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Implemented sales and marketing strategies and plans. Executed some pilots across the multiple schools such as KR Mangalam Delhi, Samhita Academy Bangalore, Arwachin International School, Delhi, MM school Jabalpur.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Successfully converted multiple schools that contributed 40% of the revenue. Introduced improvements in business strategies based on customers feedback.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Generated new business both in face to face meetings and over the phone.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Reviewed existing contracts and looking for growth opportunities. Operations Writing accurate reports through the detailed analysis of data.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Responsible for all the backend changes. Handled all school implementation process.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Introduced NLC (Neighbourhood Learning Centre) model. Managed all NLC centres. Developed creative reports.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Techniques such as SEO, PPC advertisement, Social Media Marketing. Keyword analysis and research.", "tags": []}
{"line": "ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION Qualification Duration (%) Global Institute of Technology (RTU) 2011-15", "tags": [{"ORG": "Global Institute of Technology (RTU)", "start_idx": 2388, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Global Institute of Technology (RTU)"}, {"DATE": "2011-15", "start_idx": 2425, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2011-15"}]}
{"line": "62.00 SSE Children s Academy School Alwar (RBSE) 2010-11 69.08 HSE", "tags": [{"CARDINAL": "62.00", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "62.00"}, {"ORG": "Children s Academy School", "start_idx": 10, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Children s Academy School"}, {"DATE": "2010-11", "start_idx": 49, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2010-11"}, {"CARDINAL": "69.08", "start_idx": 57, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "69.08"}]}
{"line": "Bal Bharti Sr. Sec. School Alwar (RBSE) 2008-09 77.83 B.tech (ECE)", "tags": [{"ORG": "Bal Bharti Sr. Sec. School", "start_idx": 67, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Bal Bharti Sr. Sec. School"}, {"DATE": "2008-09", "start_idx": 107, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2008-09"}, {"CARDINAL": "77.83", "start_idx": 115, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "77.83"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.tech", "start_idx": 121, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.tech"}]}
{"line": "Organization STRENGTHS Self-motivated, enthusiastic, dedicated and bear leadership qualities. Industrious and Optimistic team", "tags": []}
{"line": "Rachit Gupta E-Mail: gupta.rachit1997@gmail.com ~ Mobile: 8395061203 & 9643684600 As technology enthusiast I am looking to contribute Web Development Skills. I am currently web developer developer working on like HTML5,CSS3,PHP,DRUPAL7", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Rachit Gupta", "start_idx": 260, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Rachit Gupta"}, {"Email": "gupta.rachit1997@gmail.com", "start_idx": 281, "tag": "Email", "text": "gupta.rachit1997@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "8395061203", "start_idx": 318, "tag": "Phone", "text": "8395061203"}, {"Phone": "9643684600", "start_idx": 331, "tag": "Phone", "text": "9643684600"}, {"Designation": "web developer", "start_idx": 433, "tag": "Designation", "text": "web developer"}, {"Skills": "HTML5,CSS3,PHP,DRUPAL7", "start_idx": 473, "tag": "Skills", "text": "HTML5,CSS3,PHP,DRUPAL7"}]}
{"line": "Executive SUMMARY = Web Developer with 1.5 years of experience. Good knowledge of Html5,Css3,php, Codeigniter, Drupal7", "tags": [{"Designation": "Web Developer", "start_idx": 20, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Web Developer"}, {"ExperianceYears": "1.5 years", "start_idx": 39, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "text": "1.5 years"}, {"Skills": "Html5,Css3,php, Codeigniter, Drupal7", "start_idx": 82, "tag": "Skills", "text": "Html5,Css3,php, Codeigniter, Drupal7"}]}
{"line": "Skilled in prioritizing work and completing task with minimum supervision. Stress tolerance and has the ability to meet tight deadlines.", "tags": []}
{"line": "CAREER SUMMARY Total Experience: 1.5 years Project: Delhi Goverment , NCLT , Active car wash , Jharkhand Public Service Commission & BHEL Organization : Ornate Techno Services Designation : Junior Web Developer Experience : 1 year Key Responsibilities:", "tags": [{"ExperianceYears": "1.5 years", "start_idx": 170, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "text": "1.5 years"}, {"ORG": "Ornate Techno Services", "start_idx": 290, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Ornate Techno Services"}, {"Designation": "Junior Web Developer", "start_idx": 327, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Junior Web Developer"}, {"DATE": "1 year", "start_idx": 361, "tag": "DATE", "text": "1 year"}]}
{"line": "Web developement using php , codeigniter and Drupal7. Coding, Performing reviews, Testing, Debugging and optimization. Worked in all levels of SDLC (Requirements Analysis, Estimation, Design, Build, Test, Deployment and Support). Possess good client interaction, excellent analytical skills, problem solving, Self-motivated, Hardworking, team player, ability to handle multiple tasks, and a fast", "tags": []}
{"line": "learner. Project: Jharkhand Goverment Organization : Wonderpillars pvt ltd Designation : Junior Web Developer Experience : 6 months Key Responsibilities:", "tags": [{"ORG": "Wonderpillars pvt ltd", "start_idx": 839, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Wonderpillars pvt ltd"}, {"Designation": "Junior Web Developer", "start_idx": 875, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Junior Web Developer"}, {"DATE": "6 months", "start_idx": 909, "tag": "DATE", "text": "6 months"}]}
{"line": "Web developement using php and Drupal7. Coding, Performing reviews, Testing, Debugging and optimization. Worked in all levels of SDLC (Requirements Analysis, Estimation, Design, Build, Test, Deployment and Support). Possess good client interaction, excellent analytical skills, problem solving, Self-motivated, Hardworking, team player, ability to handle multiple tasks, and a fast learner.", "tags": []}
{"line": "BRIEF OVERVIEW B.Tech (Information Technology) from AKTU Moradabad Abilities in handling multiple priorities, with a bias for action and a genuine interest in personal and professional development.", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "B.Tech", "start_idx": 1346, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.Tech"}, {"ORG": "AKTU", "start_idx": 1383, "tag": "ORG", "text": "AKTU"}, {"GPE": "Moradabad", "start_idx": 1388, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Moradabad"}]}
{"line": "A keen communicator with excellent interpersonal skills & the ability to grasp new concepts & utilize them in a productive manner.", "tags": []}
{"line": "7/06/2019 AXP Internal 1 SCHOLASTICS 2017 2013 2010 B.Tech (Information Technology) from AKTU with 64.6% XII from Chitra Gupt Inter College School Moradabad, UP Board. X from Chitra Gupt Inter College School Moradab d, UP Board.", "tags": [{"DATE": "7/06/2019", "start_idx": 1660, "tag": "DATE", "text": "7/06/2019"}, {"ORG": "AXP Internal", "start_idx": 1670, "tag": "ORG", "text": "AXP Internal"}, {"DATE": "2017 2013 2010", "start_idx": 1697, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2017 2013 2010"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.Tech", "start_idx": 1712, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.Tech"}, {"ORG": "AKTU", "start_idx": 1749, "tag": "ORG", "text": "AKTU"}, {"CARDINAL": "64.6%", "start_idx": 1759, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "64.6%"}, {"ORG": "Chitra Gupt Inter College School Moradabad,", "start_idx": 1774, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Chitra Gupt Inter College School Moradabad,"}, {"ORG": "Chitra Gupt Inter College School Moradab", "start_idx": 1835, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Chitra Gupt Inter College School Moradab"}]}
{"line": "COMPUTER SKILLS Conversant with Html5 , Css3 , Php , CodeIgniter and CMS Drupal 7.", "tags": []}
{"line": "PERSONAL INFORMATION Date of Birth : 31-Jan-1997 Father s Name : Mr. Manoj kumar Gupta Language Known: English and Hindi I hereby declare that the information provided here is accurate and true to my belief. Date Place", "tags": [{"DOB": "31-Jan-1997", "start_idx": 2009, "tag": "DOB", "text": "31-Jan-1997"}, {"LANGUAGE": "English", "start_idx": 2075, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "English"}, {"LANGUAGE": "Hindi", "start_idx": 2087, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "Hindi"}]}
{"line": "7/06/2019 : : Noida Rachit Gupta AXP Internal", "tags": [{"DATE": "7/06/2019", "start_idx": 2191, "tag": "DATE", "text": "7/06/2019"}, {"GPE": "Noida", "start_idx": 2205, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Noida"}, {"PERSON": "Rachit Gupta", "start_idx": 2211, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Rachit Gupta"}]}
{"line": "February 2009 to May 2018 I am fire training Usha fire training Bombay", "tags": [{"DATE": "February 2009 to May 2018", "start_idx": 2424, "tag": "DATE", "text": "February 2009 to May 2018"}, {"Designation": "fire training", "start_idx": 2455, "tag": "Designation", "text": "fire training"}]}
{"line": "https://www.indeed.com/r/Tapan-kumar-Nayak/da1f5ffb3c4c4b17 isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN https://www.indeed.com/r/Tapan-kumar-Nayak/da1f5ffb3c4c4b17", "tags": []}
{"line": "Satish Kumar Ishan Tower, Near Shiv Mandir, DS Rd, Dist: Gautam Budha Nagar,", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Satish Kumar", "start_idx": 2656, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Satish Kumar"}]}
{"line": "Bhangel, Uttar Pradesh 201304 Mobile: 8700020685 E-Mail: satishumarraaz@gmail.com CAREER OBJECTIVE Seeking a position to apply the knowledge that I have learned and explore abilities, skills, towards my duties and to excel in the field of Java.", "tags": [{"GPE": "Bhangel, Uttar Pradesh", "start_idx": 2733, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Bhangel, Uttar Pradesh"}, {"Phone": "8700020685", "start_idx": 2771, "tag": "Phone", "text": "8700020685"}, {"Email": "satishumarraaz@gmail.com", "start_idx": 2790, "tag": "Email", "text": "satishumarraaz@gmail.com"}]}
{"line": "Highlights Java : Core Java Oops Concept , Exception handling, Collections, String Manipulation", "tags": []}
{"line": "Operating System: Microsoft windows 10, 8, 7.Linux, Mac. IDE: Eclipse, Note++, Net Beans, work Bench.", "tags": []}
{"line": "MySQL, Xampp, SQL Query, Database Connectivity,Hibernate Accomplishments An energetic self-motivated college graduate. Skilled in computer programming. Application support and Computer troubleshooting. Acquired knowledge in Internet Connectivity, Microsoft Windows, Application configuration. A very quick learner, skilled in communication and problem-solving.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Experience Java Developer I have done the training java in Trisect Training center at Noida from Jan 2019 to May 2019.", "tags": [{"Designation": "Java Developer", "start_idx": 3548, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Java Developer"}, {"Designation": "training", "start_idx": 3579, "tag": "Designation", "text": "training"}, {"ORG": "Trisect Training", "start_idx": 3596, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Trisect Training"}, {"GPE": "Noida", "start_idx": 3623, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Noida"}, {"DATE": "Jan 2019 to May 2019.", "start_idx": 3634, "tag": "DATE", "text": "Jan 2019 to May 2019."}]}
{"line": "Strong knowledge oops concept- Inheritance, Polymorphism, Encapsulation, Abstraction Interface, Exceptions Handling, Collections, String, Array, SQL and JDBC. Multithreading, MySQL, Xampp, SQL Query, Database Connectivity, Hibernate", "tags": []}
{"line": "Worked with Hitachi micro clinic Client side Naukri.com) As a Server support engineer June 2015 to Dec 2018", "tags": [{"ORG": "Hitachi micro clinic", "start_idx": 245, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Hitachi micro clinic"}, {"Designation": "Server support engineer", "start_idx": 295, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Server support engineer"}, {"DATE": "June 2015", "start_idx": 319, "tag": "DATE", "text": "June 2015"}, {"DATE": "Dec 2018", "start_idx": 332, "tag": "DATE", "text": "Dec 2018"}]}
{"line": "Worked with Progressive InfoTech Client side New Holland India) Ltd As Server engineer May 2014 to June 2015", "tags": [{"ORG": "Progressive InfoTech", "start_idx": 12, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Progressive InfoTech"}, {"Designation": "Server engineer", "start_idx": 71, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Server engineer"}, {"DATE": "May 2014 to June 2015", "start_idx": 87, "tag": "DATE", "text": "May 2014 to June 2015"}]}
{"line": "Worked with Global Creva Pvt Ltd Web Developer worked in HTML) May 2013 t Sep 2013", "tags": [{"ORG": "Global Creva Pvt Ltd", "start_idx": 12, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Global Creva Pvt Ltd"}, {"Designation": "Web Developer", "start_idx": 33, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Web Developer"}, {"DATE": "May 2013", "start_idx": 63, "tag": "DATE", "text": "May 2013"}, {"DATE": "Sep 2013", "start_idx": 74, "tag": "DATE", "text": "Sep 2013"}]}
{"line": "Academic Qualification 2012 B.Tech Computer Science from UPTU with 67.33% 2008 12th completed from UP board with 67%", "tags": [{"DATE": "2012", "start_idx": 23, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2012"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.Tech", "start_idx": 28, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.Tech"}, {"ORG": "UPTU", "start_idx": 57, "tag": "ORG", "text": "UPTU"}, {"CARDINAL": "67.33%", "start_idx": 67, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "67.33%"}, {"CARDINAL": "67%", "start_idx": 113, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "67%"}]}
{"line": "2006 10th completed from UP board with 69% Personal Synopsis Date of Birth: 4th July 1989", "tags": [{"CARDINAL": "69%", "start_idx": 39, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "69%"}, {"DOB": "4th July 1989", "start_idx": 76, "tag": "DOB", "text": "4th July 1989"}]}
{"line": "Father Name: Ram Kumar Status Married: Yes Current Address: Union Bank Building, Bhangel, Near Sector 82 Noida UP.", "tags": [{"GPE": "Noida UP.", "start_idx": 105, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Noida UP."}]}
{"line": "Place: (Satish Kumar)", "tags": [{"PERSON": "(Satish Kumar)", "start_idx": 159, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "(Satish Kumar)"}]}
{"line": "RESUME Krishna Kumar A10/23 DDA LIG FLATS SEC 23B DWARKA -110077", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Krishna Kumar", "start_idx": 408, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Krishna Kumar"}, {"GPE": "SEC 23B DWARKA", "start_idx": 443, "tag": "GPE", "text": "SEC 23B DWARKA"}]}
{"line": "Email:- ishangreat.kumar@gmail.com Mob: 560188073 Objective To work in an organization where professionalism and enthusiasm is recognized & to work continuously towards increasing my technical skills and professional expertise.", "tags": [{"Email": "ishangreat.kumar@gmail.com", "start_idx": 474, "tag": "Email", "text": "ishangreat.kumar@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "560188073", "start_idx": 506, "tag": "Phone", "text": "560188073"}]}
{"line": "Current Work Experience: Previous Work Experience: Magical Cloud Solutions pvt Ltd (Janakpuri) from 17th March 2016 till December 2017", "tags": [{"ORG": "Magical Cloud Solutions pvt Ltd", "start_idx": 745, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Magical Cloud Solutions pvt Ltd"}, {"DATE": "17th March 2016", "start_idx": 794, "tag": "DATE", "text": "17th March 2016"}, {"DATE": "December 2017", "start_idx": 815, "tag": "DATE", "text": "December 2017"}]}
{"line": "Web Developer PHP ,JQuery ,JavaScript, HTML Professional Qualification: 18 months higher diploma software engineering from NIIT", "tags": [{"Designation": "Web Developer", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Web Developer"}, {"DATE": "18 months", "start_idx": 72, "tag": "DATE", "text": "18 months"}, {"EducationDegree": "diploma software engineering", "start_idx": 89, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "diploma software engineering"}, {"ORG": "NIIT", "start_idx": 123, "tag": "ORG", "text": "NIIT"}]}
{"line": "three month completed specialization c from NIIT General Education : Graduate B.sc(IT) from Kuvempu university in 2015", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "B.sc(IT)", "start_idx": 78, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.sc(IT)"}, {"ORG": "Kuvempu university", "start_idx": 92, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Kuvempu university"}, {"DATE": "2015", "start_idx": 114, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2015"}]}
{"line": "Intermediate with Science stream from B.I.E.C,Patna in 2009 Matriculation from B.S.E.B , atna in 2007", "tags": [{"ORG": "B.I.E.C,Patna", "start_idx": 38, "tag": "ORG", "text": "B.I.E.C,Patna"}, {"DATE": "2009", "start_idx": 55, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2009"}, {"ORG": "B.S.E.B", "start_idx": 79, "tag": "ORG", "text": "B.S.E.B"}, {"GPE": "atna", "start_idx": 89, "tag": "GPE", "text": "atna"}, {"DATE": "2007", "start_idx": 97, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2007"}]}
{"line": "Computer Proficiency: MS Office Word, Excel, Power Point, Internet & E-mail operator", "tags": []}
{"line": "Operating system_ windows98/2000/xp,windows7 Personal Vitae: Date of Birth : 17th February 1990", "tags": [{"DOB": "17th February 1990", "start_idx": 162, "tag": "DOB", "text": "17th February 1990"}]}
{"line": "Passport : Unavailable Hobbies : Listening Music, Reading Novel & Photograph", "tags": []}
{"line": "Date : Place : ( rishna Kumar", "tags": [{"PERSON": "rishna Kumar", "start_idx": 94, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "rishna Kumar"}]}
{"line": "Mohd Aamir E-Mail: mohdaamir999993@gmail.com Mobile: +91 9999939927 CAREER OBJECTIVE To take a Challenging and High Performance oriented role in the field of Software Development and implement the expertise and experience gained in this field to develop software with efficiency and quality.", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Mohd Aamir", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Mohd Aamir"}, {"Email": "mohdaamir999993@gmail.com", "start_idx": 19, "tag": "Email", "text": "mohdaamir999993@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "9999939927", "start_idx": 57, "tag": "Phone", "text": "9999939927"}]}
{"line": "CAREER HIGHLIGHTS Aug 2018 To Feb 2019 EDGISS IT SERVICES PRIVATE LIMITED (Noida", "tags": [{"DATE": "Aug 2018", "start_idx": 310, "tag": "DATE", "text": "Aug 2018"}, {"DATE": "Feb 2019", "start_idx": 322, "tag": "DATE", "text": "Feb 2019"}, {"ORG": "EDGISS IT SERVICES PRIVATE LIMITED", "start_idx": 331, "tag": "ORG", "text": "EDGISS IT SERVICES PRIVATE LIMITED"}, {"GPE": "(Noida", "start_idx": 366, "tag": "GPE", "text": "(Noida"}]}
{"line": "TECHNICAL SKILL .Net Technologies : .NET Framework , ASP.NET , C#.NET, ,ADO.Net, jQuery", "tags": [{"Skills": ".NET Framework , ASP.NET , C#.NET, ,ADO.Net, jQuery", "start_idx": 36, "tag": "Skills", "text": ".NET Framework , ASP.NET , C#.NET, ,ADO.Net, jQuery"}]}
{"line": "Database Tool : SQL Server 2012,SQL Server 2008,PL Sql SUMMARY Strong Knowledge of OOP s Concept. Having rich experience in application development and implementation of web applications.", "tags": [{"Skills": "SQL Server 2012,SQL Server 2008,PL Sql", "start_idx": 16, "tag": "Skills", "text": "SQL Server 2012,SQL Server 2008,PL Sql"}]}
{"line": "Highly versatile and experienced in adapting and implementing the latest technologies in new application solutions. Able to work adaptively in a team as well as individually.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Possess excellent Relationship management and Team management skills with expertise in training, motivating and mentoring junior developers.", "tags": []}
{"line": "QUALIFICATION Pursuing MCA from IGNOU BCA from IGNOU Six Month training in .NET Technology.", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "Pursuing MCA", "start_idx": 518, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "Pursuing MCA"}, {"ORG": "IGNOU", "start_idx": 536, "tag": "ORG", "text": "IGNOU"}, {"EducationDegree": "BCA", "start_idx": 542, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "BCA"}, {"ORG": "IGNOU", "start_idx": 551, "tag": "ORG", "text": "IGNOU"}, {"ExperianceYears": "Six Month", "start_idx": 557, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "text": "Six Month"}, {"Designation": "training", "start_idx": 567, "tag": "Designation", "text": "training"}]}
{"line": "PROJECTS Project : Anchorage, Harrier Enterprises www.anchoragehr.com/ harrierprince.in/ Tools ASP .NET, C#,ADO.net", "tags": []}
{"line": "Role Programmer STRENGTH Responsible and hard working person with positive attitude. A very good team player with Strong problem solving skill and analytical skill.", "tags": []}
{"line": "PERSONAL DETAILS Name : Mohd Aamir Date of Birth : 01 dec 1994", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Mohd Aamir", "start_idx": 901, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Mohd Aamir"}, {"DOB": "01 dec 1994", "start_idx": 928, "tag": "DOB", "text": "01 dec 1994"}]}
{"line": "Fathers Name : Mohd Sabir Marital Status : Single Nationality : Indian", "tags": []}
{"line": "Languages Known : English ,Hindi and Urdu Current Address : House No:5265 2nd floor Kucha Rehman Ballimaran", "tags": [{"LANGUAGE": "English ,Hindi and Urdu", "start_idx": 89, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "English ,Hindi and Urdu"}]}
{"line": "(Mohd", "tags": [{"PERSON": "(Mohd", "start_idx": 315, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "(Mohd"}]}
{"line": "Shashikant Kushwaha Software Engineer Phone: 9540050922 7011286315 Address: L - 7/8, New Mahavir Nagar Tilak Nagar (New Delhi)", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Shashikant Kushwaha", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Shashikant Kushwaha"}, {"Designation": "Software Engineer", "start_idx": 20, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Software Engineer"}, {"Phone": "9540050922 7011286315", "start_idx": 45, "tag": "Phone", "text": "9540050922 7011286315"}, {"GPE": "Tilak Nagar (New Delhi)", "start_idx": 103, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Tilak Nagar (New Delhi)"}]}
{"line": "Email: rk.rohitmaurya563@gmail.com I am self-motivated, quick learner and a hard working one I can finish my work within stipulated time.", "tags": [{"Email": "rk.rohitmaurya563@gmail.com", "start_idx": 7, "tag": "Email", "text": "rk.rohitmaurya563@gmail.com"}]}
{"line": "Skills Experience Core Java Servlet JSP MySQL JavaScript HTML CSS SVG Bootstrap", "tags": [{"Skills": "Core Java Servlet JSP MySQL JavaScript HTML CSS SVG Bootstrap", "start_idx": 156, "tag": "Skills", "text": "Core Java Servlet JSP MySQL JavaScript HTML CSS SVG Bootstrap"}]}
{"line": "Educo International India Pvt. Ltd. OCTOBER 2018 - PRESENT Software Engineer", "tags": [{"ORG": "Educo International India Pvt. Ltd.", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Educo International India Pvt. Ltd."}, {"DATE": "OCTOBER 2018", "start_idx": 36, "tag": "DATE", "text": "OCTOBER 2018"}, {"DATE": "PRESENT", "start_idx": 51, "tag": "DATE", "text": "PRESENT"}, {"Designation": "Software Engineer", "start_idx": 59, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Software Engineer"}]}
{"line": "Projects Executed: Computer Based Training Software (Electronic Lecture Notes in Mathematics and Science) Client: Clark Atlanta University, Ohio University, and Moorhead State University. Tools:", "tags": []}
{"line": "HTML5, CSS3, Jquery, JavaScript Description: This project deals with the preparation of computer based training programs in mathematics and Science. It consists of detailed discussion of topics, solved examples illustration, practice sessions (testing skills of a particular student) etc for a student according to topic he/she chooses. Education", "tags": [{"Skills": "HTML5, CSS3, Jquery, JavaScript", "start_idx": 195, "tag": "Skills", "text": "HTML5, CSS3, Jquery, JavaScript"}]}
{"line": "IEC College of Engineering and Technology Greater Noida 2014 - 2018", "tags": [{"ORG": "IEC College of Engineering and Technology Greater Noida", "start_idx": 542, "tag": "ORG", "text": "IEC College of Engineering and Technology Greater Noida"}, {"DATE": "2014 - 2018", "start_idx": 598, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2014 - 2018"}]}
{"line": "B. tech Percentage : 64.9% Computer Science & Engineering Government Inter College Ghazipur", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "B. tech", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "B. tech"}, {"CARDINAL": "64.9%", "start_idx": 21, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "64.9%"}, {"ORG": "Government Inter College Ghazipur", "start_idx": 58, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Government Inter College Ghazipur"}]}
{"line": "2012 - 2014 Intermediate Percentage : 81.2% Adarsh Inter College Ghazipur High School Percentage : 81%", "tags": [{"DATE": "2012 - 2014", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2012 - 2014"}, {"CARDINAL": "81.2%", "start_idx": 38, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "81.2%"}, {"ORG": "Adarsh Inter College", "start_idx": 44, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Adarsh Inter College"}, {"CARDINAL": "81%", "start_idx": 99, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "81%"}]}
{"line": "2011 - 2012 Projects Health Book Health Book is a Web Application. This project is related to a health management system. It maintains records of all the operations that occur at any of the medical centre. The modules include namely, \"Doctor, Patient, Hospital, Blood bank\". The user level is able to", "tags": [{"DATE": "2011 - 2012", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2011 - 2012"}]}
{"line": "manage other modules such as registration, booking appointment and medical report generation.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Interest Playing Cricket Travelling Playing PC Games Strengths Self-confident and self-motivation Positive Thinking Open to any challenging work Quick Learner", "tags": []}
{"line": "WORK EXPERIENCE Developer Microsoft - Pune, Maharashtra - August 2016 to Present", "tags": [{"Designation": "Developer", "start_idx": 918, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Developer"}, {"ORG": "Microsoft", "start_idx": 928, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Microsoft"}, {"GPE": "Pune, Maharashtra", "start_idx": 940, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Pune, Maharashtra"}, {"DATE": "August 2016 to Present", "start_idx": 960, "tag": "DATE", "text": "August 2016 to Present"}]}
{"line": "Curriculum-Vitae Mohammad Tufel Phone: +91- 379106215 E-mail: morehaan25@gmail.com Career Objective: To work with an organization having creative and challenging environment where I can flourish my technical as well as personal skill and prove myself as key player in increasing name and fame of organization and my country to every corner of world", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Mohammad Tufel", "start_idx": 504, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Mohammad Tufel"}, {"Phone": "379106215", "start_idx": 531, "tag": "Phone", "text": "379106215"}, {"Email": "morehaan25@gmail.com", "start_idx": 549, "tag": "Email", "text": "morehaan25@gmail.com"}]}
{"line": ". Education Qualification: Pursuing MCA Bachelor of art in 2015 from Awadh University Faizabad", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "Pursuing MCA", "start_idx": 863, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "Pursuing MCA"}, {"DATE": "2015", "start_idx": 895, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2015"}, {"ORG": "Awadh University", "start_idx": 905, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Awadh University"}, {"GPE": "Faizabad", "start_idx": 922, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Faizabad"}]}
{"line": "Intermediate in 2012 from U.P Board Allahabad High school in 2010 from U.P Board Allahabad", "tags": [{"DATE": "2012", "start_idx": 16, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2012"}, {"ORG": "U.P Board Allahabad High school", "start_idx": 26, "tag": "ORG", "text": "U.P Board Allahabad High school"}, {"DATE": "2010", "start_idx": 61, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2010"}, {"ORG": "U.P Board Allahabad", "start_idx": 71, "tag": "ORG", "text": "U.P Board Allahabad"}]}
{"line": "Other Qualification: DCA (Diploma in computer application) Completed 2016. CCC (Computer Concept Course )", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "DCA (Diploma in computer application)", "start_idx": 21, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "DCA (Diploma in computer application)"}, {"DATE": "2016.", "start_idx": 69, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2016."}]}
{"line": "Certification: Certification Course in PHP - (2017) Work Experience: Working As Web Developer Profile in Astrodevam.com Pvt Ltd Sector 18, Noida Uttar Pradesh (201301) From July- 2018 To Still date.", "tags": [{"Designation": "Web Developer", "start_idx": 186, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Web Developer"}, {"ORG": "Astrodevam.com Pvt Ltd", "start_idx": 211, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Astrodevam.com Pvt Ltd"}, {"GPE": "Noida", "start_idx": 245, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Noida"}, {"DATE": "July- 2018", "start_idx": 279, "tag": "DATE", "text": "July- 2018"}]}
{"line": "Technical Skills: Language: Core PHP , HTML, Css ,Java Script And Photoshop", "tags": [{"Skills": "Core PHP , HTML, Css ,Java Script And Photoshop", "start_idx": 333, "tag": "Skills", "text": "Core PHP , HTML, Css ,Java Script And Photoshop"}]}
{"line": "CMS & Framework: Word Press, Basic About Codeigniter Database: MySQL, Training: PHP", "tags": []}
{"line": "Listening to Songs and Surfing Net. Projects: https://astrodevam.com/ http://vindhyachalmata.com/ http://originalparad.com/ http://horoscope.astrodevam.com/", "tags": []}
{"line": "www.realrudraksha.com http://vindhyachalmata.com/hindi/ Language Known: Hindi: Read, Write, Speak English: Read, Write, Speak", "tags": []}
{"line": "Personal Details: Name : Mohammad Tufel Date-of-Birth : 14-Oct-1994 Father Name : Mr. Vakeel", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Mohammad Tufel", "start_idx": 498, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Mohammad Tufel"}, {"DOB": "14-Oct-1994", "start_idx": 529, "tag": "DOB", "text": "14-Oct-1994"}]}
{"line": "Gender : Male Marital Status : Single Nationality : Indian Address : Noida sector 15 (U.P) -201301- India", "tags": []}
{"line": "Date: Place: Noida (U.P)", "tags": [{"GPE": "Noida (U.P)", "start_idx": 874, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Noida (U.P)"}]}
{"line": "CURRICULAM VITAE RAJESH KUMAR SRIVASTAVA Mobile No: - +91- 905657746 +91- 005456104", "tags": [{"PERSON": "RAJESH KUMAR SRIVASTAVA", "start_idx": 17, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "RAJESH KUMAR SRIVASTAVA"}, {"Phone": "905657746", "start_idx": 59, "tag": "Phone", "text": "905657746"}, {"Phone": "005456104", "start_idx": 74, "tag": "Phone", "text": "005456104"}]}
{"line": "Email Id: rikki.rajesh@gmail.com Objective Seeking a position in an Organization to utilize my experience and knowledge in the field of Information Technology for development of Organization.", "tags": [{"Email": "rikki.rajesh@gmail.com", "start_idx": 10, "tag": "Email", "text": "rikki.rajesh@gmail.com"}]}
{"line": "Overview Keen learner with constant zest to acquire new skills. Able to adapt new environment and work in any project. A self-starter-initiative, enthusiastic and ability to learn quickly. Exceptional experience in bidding online and generating revenue. Huge knowledge of drafting business proposals. Good understanding of online bidding process. Very interactive and co-operative & Good Communication", "tags": []}
{"line": "skills. Ability & inclination to communicate openly and honestly. Comfortable working in flexible timings, if required. Familiarity with common terminology used in Web development. Good written and verbal communication skills", "tags": []}
{"line": "Professional Experience Working as Business Development Executive in Phoenix Media Pvt. Ltd. in Kaushambi, haziabad (From 18 Jul 2018 to 31 Aug 2019 . 6 Months internship experience as a Software Developer on Asp.net in IQRA Software Technologies Pvt Ltd Lucknow.", "tags": [{"Designation": "Business Development Executive", "start_idx": 855, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Business Development Executive"}, {"ORG": "Phoenix Media Pvt. Ltd.", "start_idx": 889, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Phoenix Media Pvt. Ltd."}, {"GPE": "haziabad", "start_idx": 927, "tag": "GPE", "text": "haziabad"}, {"DATE": "18 Jul 2018", "start_idx": 942, "tag": "DATE", "text": "18 Jul 2018"}, {"DATE": "31 Aug 2019", "start_idx": 957, "tag": "DATE", "text": "31 Aug 2019"}, {"ExperianceYears": "6 Months", "start_idx": 971, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "text": "6 Months"}, {"Designation": "internship", "start_idx": 980, "tag": "Designation", "text": "internship"}, {"Designation": "Software Developer", "start_idx": 1007, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Software Developer"}, {"ORG": "IQRA Software Technologies Pvt Ltd", "start_idx": 1040, "tag": "ORG", "text": "IQRA Software Technologies Pvt Ltd"}]}
{"line": "Job Responsibil ty Building business relationships with current and potential clients. Understanding client needs and offering solutions and support answering potential client questions and follow-up call questions. Bidding and New business generation on Freelancer, Upwork etc. Fixing issue of website, content uploading. Creating and maintaining a list/database of prospect clients maintaining", "tags": [{"GPE": "ty", "start_idx": 1100, "tag": "GPE", "text": "ty"}]}
{"line": "database (ExcelSheet) of prospective client information. Documentation (experience in proposal writing) Meet the assigned monthly targets. Managed all communication with clients to convert all bids.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Educational Qualification Graduation Bachelor of Computer Application from Awadhoot Bhagwan Ram PG College Anpara under MGKVP University, Varanasi (UP) in 2014. 12th from CBSE Board in 2011. 10th from U.P. Board in 2009.", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "Bachelor of Computer Application", "start_idx": 1848, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "Bachelor of Computer Application"}, {"ORG": "Awadhoot Bhagwan Ram PG College", "start_idx": 1886, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Awadhoot Bhagwan Ram PG College"}, {"ORG": "MGKVP", "start_idx": 1931, "tag": "ORG", "text": "MGKVP"}, {"GPE": "Varanasi", "start_idx": 1949, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Varanasi"}, {"DATE": "2014. 12th", "start_idx": 1966, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2014. 12th"}, {"ORG": "CBSE Board", "start_idx": 1982, "tag": "ORG", "text": "CBSE Board"}, {"DATE": "2011. 10th", "start_idx": 1996, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2011. 10th"}, {"ORG": "U.P. Board", "start_idx": 2012, "tag": "ORG", "text": "U.P. Board"}, {"DATE": "2009.", "start_idx": 2026, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2009."}]}
{"line": "Personal Information Date of Birth Father s Name Mother s Name Sex Nationality Address(Home) Marital status Languages Known Hobbies Strengths", "tags": []}
{"line": ": 15thFeb, 1994 : Mr. Shri Prakash Srivastava : Mrs. Bina Srivastava : Male : Indian : MM-157 Sec-D1 LDA Colony Kanpur Road Lucknow 226012 : Single : Hindi, English : Watching movies, playi g cricket : Positive Attitude, Smart Worker, &Keen Learner", "tags": [{"DOB": "15thFeb, 1994", "start_idx": 144, "tag": "DOB", "text": "15thFeb, 1994"}, {"GPE": "Lucknow", "start_idx": 266, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Lucknow"}, {"LANGUAGE": "movies, playi", "start_idx": 318, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "movies, playi"}]}
{"line": "Declaration I hereby declare that the above stated information is true and correct. If given an opportunity in your esteemed organization I will perform my duties to your utmost satisfaction.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Date: (Rajesh Kumar", "tags": [{"PERSON": "(Rajesh Kumar", "start_idx": 589, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "(Rajesh Kumar"}]}
{"line": "Hemendra Yadav Vill-Lakhan,Pilkhuwa Ghaziabad, Pin Code:245304 Contact: +91- 954099115 9667850624 Email: emendrayadav9607@gmail.com", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Hemendra Yadav", "start_idx": 168, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Hemendra Yadav"}, {"Phone": "954099115 9667850624", "start_idx": 245, "tag": "Phone", "text": "954099115 9667850624"}, {"Email": "emendrayadav9607@gmail.com", "start_idx": 273, "tag": "Email", "text": "emendrayadav9607@gmail.com"}]}
{"line": "Career Objective: Seeking for a job to pursue a highly rewarding career and healthy work environment where I can utilize my skills and knowledge efficiently for the organizational growth.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Academic Qualification: Degree/Course MCA BCA Class XII Class X Institution Board/University", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "MCA BCA", "start_idx": 226, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "MCA BCA"}]}
{"line": "Year Percentage ABES Engineering College AKTU 2019 69.14% Sunderdeep College Mgmt&Tech", "tags": [{"ORG": "ABES Engineering College", "start_idx": 297, "tag": "ORG", "text": "ABES Engineering College"}, {"DATE": "2019", "start_idx": 327, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2019"}, {"CARDINAL": "69.14%", "start_idx": 332, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "69.14%"}, {"ORG": "Sunderdeep College", "start_idx": 339, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Sunderdeep College"}]}
{"line": "C.C.S.University 2017 61.36% T.S.Inter College U.P. 2014 60.2% S.N.Bhatt HS School", "tags": [{"ORG": "C.C.S.University", "start_idx": 368, "tag": "ORG", "text": "C.C.S.University"}, {"DATE": "2017", "start_idx": 385, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2017"}, {"CARDINAL": "61.36%", "start_idx": 390, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "61.36%"}, {"ORG": "T.S.Inter College", "start_idx": 397, "tag": "ORG", "text": "T.S.Inter College"}, {"CARDINAL": "60.2%", "start_idx": 425, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "60.2%"}, {"ORG": "S.N.Bhatt HS School", "start_idx": 431, "tag": "ORG", "text": "S.N.Bhatt HS School"}]}
{"line": "U.P. 2012 78% Key Skills: Language : C, PHP , Python", "tags": [{"CARDINAL": "78%", "start_idx": 10, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "78%"}, {"Skills": "C, PHP , Python", "start_idx": 37, "tag": "Skills", "text": "C, PHP , Python"}]}
{"line": "Packages : MS-office DBMS : Sql-server, Oracle Framework : Django, Operating System", "tags": []}
{"line": ": Windows 7, 10 Area of interest: Developing,Testing, Database Project Details:", "tags": []}
{"line": "Title : Online Ticket Reservation Front End : PHP,HTML, JavaScript Back End", "tags": []}
{"line": ": PHP Description : This system is designed to provide the facility where the customer can easily reserve ticket online .This project is not difficult to operate and understood by the users.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Title : SMART SHOP Front End : HTML, CSS, JavaScript Back End", "tags": []}
{"line": ": Python Framework : Django Description : Smart Shop will be leading destination for online shopping in India, offering some of the best prices and a completely hassle-free experience with options of paying through Cash on Delivery, Debit Card, Credit Card and Net Banking processed through secure and trusted gateways.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Internship: Working as web developer in Python Pursuing in Agile Softech pvt.ltd", "tags": [{"Designation": "web developer", "start_idx": 836, "tag": "Designation", "text": "web developer"}, {"ORG": "Agile Softech pvt.ltd", "start_idx": 872, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Agile Softech pvt.ltd"}]}
{"line": "Achievements: Participating Uttar Pradesh Scout&Guide at district and mandal level also third step contest", "tags": []}
{"line": "Coordinator (SAPTRANG Annual fest ( CA Dept)), haziabad Personal Snippets: Father s name", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "CA", "start_idx": 143, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "CA"}, {"GPE": "haziabad", "start_idx": 154, "tag": "GPE", "text": "haziabad"}]}
{"line": ": Mr. Mahesh Pal Yadav Date of Birth : 28th June, 1997", "tags": [{"DOB": "28th June, 1997", "start_idx": 235, "tag": "DOB", "text": "28th June, 1997"}]}
{"line": "Language Known : English and Hindi Hobbies : Playing Cricket,Watching", "tags": [{"LANGUAGE": "English", "start_idx": 17, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "English"}, {"LANGUAGE": "Hindi", "start_idx": 29, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "Hindi"}]}
{"line": "Viny Khandelwal Self-employed in Family Business - SELF EMPLOYED Kullu, Himachal Pradesh - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Viny- Khandelwal/02e488f477e2f5bc", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Viny Khandelwal", "start_idx": 70, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Viny Khandelwal"}, {"Designation": "SELF EMPLOYED", "start_idx": 121, "tag": "Designation", "text": "SELF EMPLOYED"}, {"GPE": "Kullu, Himachal Pradesh", "start_idx": 135, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Kullu, Himachal Pradesh"}]}
{"line": "Currently pursuing my certifications in Digital Marketing. 2 year's experience in managing, maintaining and assisting to run a camping site. Additional experience in event managing and emcee in Army Wife Welfare Association (NGO) 1-year self-employed in Kudi Firang 2 years of work experience in Infrastructure Management and Support in TCS Worked as Soft skill trainer in TCS", "tags": [{"ORG": "Digital Marketing.", "start_idx": 268, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Digital Marketing."}, {"ExperianceYears": "2 year's", "start_idx": 287, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "text": "2 year's"}, {"ORG": "Army Wife Welfare Association", "start_idx": 422, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Army Wife Welfare Association"}, {"ORG": "Kudi Firang", "start_idx": 482, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Kudi Firang"}, {"ExperianceYears": "2 years of work experience", "start_idx": 494, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "text": "2 years of work experience"}, {"ORG": "Infrastructure Management and Support", "start_idx": 524, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Infrastructure Management and Support"}, {"ORG": "TCS", "start_idx": 565, "tag": "ORG", "text": "TCS"}, {"ORG": "TCS", "start_idx": 601, "tag": "ORG", "text": "TCS"}]}
{"line": "Worked as Operation Analyst for Microsoft Server management team. Worked as Application Support engineer for PricewaterhouseCoopers, USA. Worked as Technical Support for Microsoft Office, Outlook and PowerPoint.", "tags": [{"Designation": "Operation Analyst", "start_idx": 10, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Operation Analyst"}, {"ORG": "Microsoft Server", "start_idx": 32, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Microsoft Server"}, {"Designation": "Application Support engineer", "start_idx": 76, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Application Support engineer"}, {"ORG": "PricewaterhouseCoopers, USA.", "start_idx": 109, "tag": "ORG", "text": "PricewaterhouseCoopers, USA."}, {"Designation": "Technical Support", "start_idx": 148, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Technical Support"}]}
{"line": "WORK EXPERIENCE Self-employed in Family Business SELF EMPLOYED - February 2015 to Present", "tags": [{"Designation": "Self-employed", "start_idx": 228, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Self-employed"}, {"DATE": "February 2015", "start_idx": 277, "tag": "DATE", "text": "February 2015"}, {"DATE": "Present", "start_idx": 294, "tag": "DATE", "text": "Present"}]}
{"line": "Systems Engineer Microsoft Corporation - Hyderabad Telangana - October 2012 to January 2015", "tags": [{"Designation": "Systems Engineer", "start_idx": 271, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Systems Engineer"}, {"ORG": "Microsoft Corporation", "start_idx": 288, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Microsoft Corporation"}, {"GPE": "Hyderabad Telangana", "start_idx": 312, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Hyderabad Telangana"}, {"DATE": "October 2012 to January 2015", "start_idx": 334, "tag": "DATE", "text": "October 2012 to January 2015"}]}
{"line": "tasks, datacenter server deployments and hardware procurement/replacement follow-ups. 2. PwC Application Support", "tags": []}
{"line": "Client: PricewaterhouseCoopers. Role: Incident management and other applications for corporates and firms in USA.", "tags": []}
{"line": "https://www.indeed.com/r/Viny-Khandelwal/02e488f477e2f5bc isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN https://www.indeed.com/r/Viny-Khandelwal/02e488f477e2f5bc isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN Responsibilities: Handling deployment of firm application upgrades and reporting of bugs and errors to development team, SLA and quality report submission and training agents according to new updates and best practices shared, attending team meetings for process development and improvement, maintain existing and generate new operational support", "tags": []}
{"line": "documentation, communicating with 3rd party service providers for account activations, upgrades, password resets and membership renewals, troubleshooting system software and hardware configuration issues, log issue and user contact into customer database, translate end-user business needs into working solutions.", "tags": []}
{"line": "EDUCATION Bachelor of Engineering in Digital Marketing Nitte Meenakshi Institute of Technology - Bengaluru Karnataka", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "Bachelor of Engineering", "start_idx": 1577, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "Bachelor of Engineering"}, {"ORG": "Nitte Meenakshi Institute of Technology", "start_idx": 1622, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Nitte Meenakshi Institute of Technology"}, {"GPE": "Bengaluru Karnataka", "start_idx": 1664, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Bengaluru Karnataka"}]}
{"line": "SKILLS EXCHANGE (Less than 1 year), HTML (Less than 1 year), KITCHEN (Less than 1 year), LINUX (Less than 1 year), VMWARE (Less than 1 year)", "tags": [{"Skills": "EXCHANGE (Less than 1 year), HTML (Less than 1 year), KITCHEN (Less than 1 year), LINUX (Less than 1 year), VMWARE (Less than 1 year)", "start_idx": 7, "tag": "Skills", "text": "EXCHANGE (Less than 1 year), HTML (Less than 1 year), KITCHEN (Less than 1 year), LINUX (Less than 1 year), VMWARE (Less than 1 year)"}]}
{"line": "PERSONAL DOSSIER Name: Viny Khandelwal Phone: [ ] Email: khandelwal.viny@gmail.com Husband's Name: Capt. Anuj Mahant", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Viny Khandelwal", "start_idx": 276, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Viny Khandelwal"}, {"Email": "khandelwal.viny@gmail.com", "start_idx": 310, "tag": "Email", "text": "khandelwal.viny@gmail.com"}]}
{"line": "Permanent Address: HNO - 240, Gandhinagar, Dhalpur, [", "tags": []}
{"line": "Space auditing Microsoft - 2017 to 2017 Auditing the space. EDUCATION", "tags": [{"ORG": "Microsoft", "start_idx": 543, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Microsoft"}, {"DATE": "2017", "start_idx": 555, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2017"}]}
{"line": "Vijaya main Vijaya SKILLS Good listener,take up responsibilities,good at communication,great at taking challenges,excellent in various sports like soccer,cricket,kabbadi,cycling,running,swimming, fluent in English,kannada, known languages hindi,tail,telugu", "tags": []}
{"line": "https://www.indeed.com/r/Anand-S/ce230cad6115ae68", "tags": []}
{"line": "Tavarekere - Bengaluru, Karnataka - 2015 to 2015 560029 EDUCATION B.Tech", "tags": [{"GPE": "Bengaluru, Karnataka", "start_idx": 13, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Bengaluru, Karnataka"}, {"DATE": "2015 to 2015", "start_idx": 36, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2015 to 2015"}, {"EducationDegree": "B.Tech", "start_idx": 66, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.Tech"}]}
{"line": "Akshay Dubey Actively looking for opportunity in .NET Development Pune Maharashtra - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Akshay-Dubey/87dcd40b335e6ffa", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Akshay Dubey", "start_idx": 172, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Akshay Dubey"}, {"GPE": "Pune Maharashtra", "start_idx": 238, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Pune Maharashtra"}]}
{"line": "To work in a challenging environment that will test me at all level and allow me to utilize my professional as well as personal skills by way of positive contribution to the organization.", "tags": []}
{"line": "by the CEO of Microsoft, Satya Nadella; and TechDays or DevCon (Developer Conference)", "tags": []}
{"line": "Web Link: https://akshaydubey.wordpress.com/ Microsoft Student Associate MICROSOFT - July 2014 to December 2015", "tags": [{"ORG": "MICROSOFT", "start_idx": 973, "tag": "ORG", "text": "MICROSOFT"}, {"DATE": "July 2014", "start_idx": 985, "tag": "DATE", "text": "July 2014"}, {"DATE": "December 2015", "start_idx": 998, "tag": "DATE", "text": "December 2015"}]}
{"line": "emulator. https://www.indeed.com/r/Akshay-Dubey/87dcd40b335e6ffa isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN Promoting and building city-level Microsoft Student User Group collaborating with other MSPs.", "tags": []}
{"line": "EDUCATION B.E Sinhgad Institute 2016 HSC Maharashtra State - Lonavale Maharashtra", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "B.E", "start_idx": 1085, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.E"}, {"ORG": "Sinhgad Institute", "start_idx": 1089, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Sinhgad Institute"}, {"DATE": "2016", "start_idx": 1107, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2016"}, {"GPE": "Lonavale Maharashtra", "start_idx": 1136, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Lonavale Maharashtra"}]}
{"line": "2012 SSC Maharashtra State 2010 Technology & Science Pune University - Lonavale Maharashtra", "tags": [{"DATE": "2012", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2012"}, {"ORG": "Pune University", "start_idx": 53, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Pune University"}, {"GPE": "Lonavale Maharashtra", "start_idx": 71, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Lonavale Maharashtra"}]}
{"line": "SKILLS .NET (3 years), ASP (1 year), ASP.NET (1 year), C# (1 year), databases. (1 year), C++, Css, Javascript, Html, C", "tags": [{"Skills": ".NET (3 years), ASP (1 year), ASP.NET (1 year), C# (1 year), databases. (1 year), C++, Css, Javascript, Html, C", "start_idx": 7, "tag": "Skills", "text": ".NET (3 years), ASP (1 year), ASP.NET (1 year), C# (1 year), databases. (1 year), C++, Css, Javascript, Html, C"}]}
{"line": "Databases", "tags": []}
{"line": "Avinash Kumar Software Testing Engineer An IT professional with experience, speci cally in Functional Testing, Mobile App Testing, Localization Testing, Quality Control. Working on large delivery projects based on E-Learning domain, EPrescription. Avinash is a dynamic team member who is consistently working towards success and completion of projects with an ability to work", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Avinash Kumar", "start_idx": 103, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Avinash Kumar"}, {"Designation": "Software Testing Engineer", "start_idx": 117, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Software Testing Engineer"}, {"PERSON": "Avinash", "start_idx": 351, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Avinash"}]}
{"line": "independently. arya.avinash92@gmail.com WORK EXPERIENCE Software Testing Engineer QAInfotech Pvt Ltd +919471282112", "tags": [{"Email": "arya.avinash92@gmail.com", "start_idx": 494, "tag": "Email", "text": "arya.avinash92@gmail.com"}, {"Designation": "Software Testing Engineer", "start_idx": 535, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Software Testing Engineer"}, {"ORG": "QAInfotech Pvt Ltd", "start_idx": 561, "tag": "ORG", "text": "QAInfotech Pvt Ltd"}, {"Phone": "+919471282112", "start_idx": 580, "tag": "Phone", "text": "+919471282112"}]}
{"line": "Achievements/Tasks 5 Months of experience in QA Infotech on Software Testing Manual Testing", "tags": [{"ExperianceYears": "5 Months", "start_idx": 19, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "text": "5 Months"}, {"ORG": "QA Infotech", "start_idx": 45, "tag": "ORG", "text": "QA Infotech"}, {"Designation": "Software Testing Manual Testing", "start_idx": 60, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Software Testing Manual Testing"}]}
{"line": "Delhi India Basic knowledge of Jira, Bugzilla, Postman, JMeter and Selenium Experience in di erent phases of testing which includes Smoke, Sanity, Regression, Integration, System Testing, Load Testing, Functional Testing and Performance Testing", "tags": [{"GPE": "Delhi India", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Delhi India"}]}
{"line": "SKILLS Software Testing Life Cycle Good knowledge of Software Testing Life Cycle Experience in all stages of Software Development Life cycle Experience in testing of Web based and Client/Server applications on Di erent environment Extensive experience in Black box Testing.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Mobile Application testing Agile Methodology CERTIFICATES ISTQB Certi ed Tester Foundation Level UK Based", "tags": []}
{"line": "Database Management System, SQL Selenium JMeter Postman QTP Bugzilla, JIRA Functional Testing", "tags": []}
{"line": "LANGUAGES English Full Professional Pro ciency Hindi PROJECTS ZappRx Project Details: ZappRx is an application for prescription management that allows healthcare providers, patients, and pharmacists to more easily interact and communicate. When a provider writes an e-prescription using ZappRx, the patient instantly receives the prescription on their smartphone and can easily ll, transfer,", "tags": [{"LANGUAGE": "English", "start_idx": 729, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "English"}, {"LANGUAGE": "Hindi", "start_idx": 766, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "Hindi"}]}
{"line": "or renew it. ZappRx provides a secure collaborative online platform that allows patients, physicians and pharmacists to work together to improve patients access to treatment, delivering medicine faster, with fewer hassles and greater transparency.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Roles & Responsibility Review the work conducted by Software Testing Trainee Analyzing requirement/design speci cation, developing test cases and participate in test case peer review. Testing, debugging and diagnosing errors and faults in an application to ensure programs and applications perform to speci cation. Testing, debugging and diagnosing errors and faults in an application to ensure programs and", "tags": [{"Designation": "Software Testing Trainee", "start_idx": 1411, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Software Testing Trainee"}]}
{"line": "applications perform to speci cation. Identifying potential bugs and issues and escalate appropriately. Document results of the tests performed, including identi cation and follow-up of issues.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Full Professional Pro ciency INTERESTS Listening music EDUCATION B.Tech Maharishi Markandeshwar Ambala, Punjab", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "B.Tech", "start_idx": 2026, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "B.Tech"}, {"ORG": "Maharishi Markandeshwar", "start_idx": 2033, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Maharishi Markandeshwar"}, {"GPE": "Ambala, Punjab", "start_idx": 2057, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Ambala, Punjab"}]}
{"line": "ACHIEVEMENTS I was the member of Art of living team as I loved doing Meditation for Long Hours and yoga which keeps my Mind sharp, enthusiastic and", "tags": []}
{"line": "Priyansh Kumar Email: priyansh_shiraj@outlook.com Add: 435-436, Sector 8 Mob: 8006377600 Jagriti Vihar, Meerut", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Priyansh Kumar", "start_idx": 148, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Priyansh Kumar"}, {"Email": "priyansh_shiraj@outlook.com", "start_idx": 170, "tag": "Email", "text": "priyansh_shiraj@outlook.com"}, {"Phone": "8006377600", "start_idx": 226, "tag": "Phone", "text": "8006377600"}, {"GPE": "Meerut", "start_idx": 252, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Meerut"}]}
{"line": "Uttar Pradesh, India Education B. Tech (CS) 2008-2013 IIMT ENGINEERING COLLEGE", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "B. Tech", "start_idx": 31, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "B. Tech"}, {"DATE": "2008-2013", "start_idx": 44, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2008-2013"}, {"ORG": "IIMT ENGINEERING COLLEGE", "start_idx": 54, "tag": "ORG", "text": "IIMT ENGINEERING COLLEGE"}]}
{"line": "GATE 2012 (Qualified) Objective Seeking a challenging software development opportunity in a dynamic", "tags": [{"DATE": "2012", "start_idx": 5, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2012"}]}
{"line": "environment where innovation, education and sense of ownership are valued and encouraged.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Profile I am keen to learn new skills and enjoy working in software and learning new things.", "tags": []}
{"line": "I am a good observer and I always try to improve myself to maintain a positive aura around me.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Skills HTML, PHP, MySQL Worked on CMS Blog Project Learning CSS", "tags": [{"Skills": "HTML, PHP, MySQL", "start_idx": 385, "tag": "Skills", "text": "HTML, PHP, MySQL"}]}
{"line": "Learning JavaScript Familiar with Windows OS, and Ubuntu Hobbies Reading Classics and", "tags": []}
{"line": "VIMLESH KR. VICKY Email: vickycse15@gmail.com Mobile: 80057571854 C AREER O BJECTIVE Intend to build a career in competitive atmosphere to learn and grow with leading corporate of hi-tech environment and willing to work as a key player in the challenging and creative environment.", "tags": [{"PERSON": "VIMLESH KR. VICKY", "start_idx": 528, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "VIMLESH KR. VICKY"}, {"Email": "vickycse15@gmail.com", "start_idx": 553, "tag": "Email", "text": "vickycse15@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "80057571854", "start_idx": 582, "tag": "Phone", "text": "80057571854"}]}
{"line": "E DUCATIONAL Q UALIFICATIONS COURSE Btech (Computer Science Engg.) Class XII", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "Btech", "start_idx": 845, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "Btech"}]}
{"line": "Class x NAME OF INSTITUTE UNIVERSITY /BOARD College of Engineering & Rajasthan Technical Technology University Bikaner Public School CBSE (DELHI) Darbhanga Bela C.S.V.P CBSE (DELHI) Kanti(Muzzafarpur)", "tags": [{"ORG": "College of Engineering & Rajasthan Technical Technology", "start_idx": 930, "tag": "ORG", "text": "College of Engineering & Rajasthan Technical Technology"}, {"ORG": "Bikaner Public School", "start_idx": 997, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Bikaner Public School"}]}
{"line": "T ECHNICAL PROFICIENCY CGPA YEAR OF /PERCENTAGE PASSING 61.8% 2018 66.0%", "tags": [{"CARDINAL": "61.8%", "start_idx": 1143, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "61.8%"}, {"DATE": "2018", "start_idx": 1149, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2018"}, {"CARDINAL": "66.0%", "start_idx": 1154, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "66.0%"}]}
{"line": "2014 95.0% 2011 Eight months working experience at Primezone Infotech Pvt. Ltd. (Noida)", "tags": [{"DATE": "2014", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2014"}, {"CARDINAL": "95.0%", "start_idx": 5, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "95.0%"}, {"DATE": "2011", "start_idx": 11, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2011"}, {"ExperianceYears": "Eight months", "start_idx": 16, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "text": "Eight months"}, {"ORG": "Primezone Infotech Pvt. Ltd.", "start_idx": 51, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Primezone Infotech Pvt. Ltd."}, {"GPE": "(Noida)", "start_idx": 80, "tag": "GPE", "text": "(Noida)"}]}
{"line": "Good working experience of core PHP. Worked on wordpress websites. Also have knowledge of CakePHP", "tags": []}
{"line": "P ROJECT E XPOSURE Project : CRM- for gas agency - An ngo Website of Bhagawatgeeta - Ayurveda online store", "tags": []}
{"line": "T RAINING ATTENDED . Summer Research Project-I Primezone Infotech Pvt. Ltd Noida) (PHP) [ ay 17-July 17", "tags": [{"ORG": "Primezone Infotech Pvt. Ltd", "start_idx": 252, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Primezone Infotech Pvt. Ltd"}, {"GPE": "Noida)", "start_idx": 280, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Noida)"}, {"DATE": "ay 17-July 17", "start_idx": 295, "tag": "DATE", "text": "ay 17-July 17"}]}
{"line": "Web Page Development WordPress XAMPP Server Skillset Programming Languages: C, C++, JaVa", "tags": []}
{"line": "Software Packages:VLSI Design Software ,VHDL, MATLAB Participations Big Data & Hadoop Workshop at IIT Roorkee [ March 2017]", "tags": []}
{"line": "Event Organizing member of RISONANZA at college [2017] Web Design Workshop", "tags": []}
{"line": "2004 Diploma in Comput r Applicat on Mac infotech", "tags": [{"GPE": "in Comput", "start_idx": 1004, "tag": "GPE", "text": "in Comput"}, {"GPE": "Applicat", "start_idx": 1016, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Applicat"}]}
{"line": "PHP DEVELOPER WITH 8 MONTH EXPERIENCE Pankaj pankaj.shishodia11@gmail.com 8755728373 CAREER OBJECTIVE I want to secure a position in an organization who provides me an opportunity to face diverse problems and enable me", "tags": [{"Designation": "PHP DEVELOPER", "start_idx": 1041, "tag": "Designation", "text": "PHP DEVELOPER"}, {"ExperianceYears": "8 MONTH EXPERIENCE", "start_idx": 1060, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "text": "8 MONTH EXPERIENCE"}, {"PERSON": "Pankaj", "start_idx": 1079, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Pankaj"}, {"Email": "pankaj.shishodia11@gmail.com", "start_idx": 1086, "tag": "Email", "text": "pankaj.shishodia11@gmail.com"}, {"Phone": "8755728373", "start_idx": 1115, "tag": "Phone", "text": "8755728373"}]}
{"line": "SKILLS Front End - HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP Back End- PHP Scripting language- Javascript, Jquery, Ajax Database- MYSQL Framework- Codeigniter EXPERIENCE Oct-2018 - Jun-2019", "tags": [{"Skills": "HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP", "start_idx": 1279, "tag": "Skills", "text": "HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP"}, {"Skills": "Javascript, Jquery, Ajax", "start_idx": 1334, "tag": "Skills", "text": "Javascript, Jquery, Ajax"}, {"DATE": "Oct-2018 - Jun-2019", "start_idx": 1409, "tag": "DATE", "text": "Oct-2018 - Jun-2019"}]}
{"line": "PHP Developer Humanlinks technology pvt ltd PHP Developer PROJECTS Project Name: Online Voting system Role: Both front end and backend", "tags": [{"Designation": "PHP Developer", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "Designation", "text": "PHP Developer"}, {"ORG": "Humanlinks technology pvt ltd", "start_idx": 14, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Humanlinks technology pvt ltd"}, {"Designation": "PHP Developer", "start_idx": 44, "tag": "Designation", "text": "PHP Developer"}]}
{"line": "Team Size: 2 Project Duration: 3 Month Front End- HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP Back End - PHP Database- MYSQL Project Name: Business Gaming Role: Both frontend and backend", "tags": []}
{"line": "Team Size: 3 Front End - HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP Back End - PHP Scripting - Javascript, Jquery, Ajax Database- MYSQL Framework- Codeigniter", "tags": []}
{"line": "EDUCATION Degree/Course Institute/College University/Board Percentage/ CGPA Year of Passing MCA ABES EC Ghaziabad", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "MCA", "start_idx": 528, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "MCA"}, {"ORG": "ABES EC", "start_idx": 532, "tag": "ORG", "text": "ABES EC"}, {"GPE": "Ghaziabad", "start_idx": 540, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Ghaziabad"}]}
{"line": "AKTU Lucknow 68 % 2017 BCA RVHETI Dadri CCSU Meerut 64 %", "tags": [{"ORG": "AKTU", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "ORG", "text": "AKTU"}, {"CARDINAL": "68 %", "start_idx": 13, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "68 %"}, {"DATE": "2017", "start_idx": 18, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2017"}, {"EducationDegree": "BCA", "start_idx": 23, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "BCA"}, {"ORG": "RVHETI Dadri CCSU Meerut", "start_idx": 27, "tag": "ORG", "text": "RVHETI Dadri CCSU Meerut"}, {"CARDINAL": "64 %", "start_idx": 52, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "64 %"}]}
{"line": "2015 12 VRSB IC Kalaunda Dadri UP Board 60 % 2012", "tags": [{"DATE": "2015 12", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2015 12"}, {"ORG": "VRSB IC", "start_idx": 8, "tag": "ORG", "text": "VRSB IC"}, {"PERSON": "Kalaunda Dadri", "start_idx": 16, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Kalaunda Dadri"}, {"CARDINAL": "60 %", "start_idx": 40, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "60 %"}, {"DATE": "2012", "start_idx": 45, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2012"}]}
{"line": "10 Anshu Public IC Dadri UP Board 56 % 2010 STRENGTHS", "tags": [{"DATE": "10", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "DATE", "text": "10"}, {"ORG": "IC Dadri UP Board", "start_idx": 16, "tag": "ORG", "text": "IC Dadri UP Board"}, {"CARDINAL": "56 %", "start_idx": 34, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "56 %"}, {"DATE": "2010", "start_idx": 39, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2010"}]}
{"line": "Hard working Good team member Punctual Self motivated Quick learner AREAS OF INTERESTS Web development", "tags": []}
{"line": "HOBBIES Listening Music Playing cricket Travelling PERSONAL DETAILS Address Vill- Gulaothi(Khurd) Post- Jarcha Dist.- Gautam Buddh Nagar", "tags": []}
{"line": "Languages Known Hindi and English", "tags": [{"LANGUAGE": "Hindi", "start_idx": 388, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "Hindi"}, {"LANGUAGE": "English", "start_idx": 398, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "English"}]}
{"line": "Ganesh AlalaSundaram A Dev-Test Professional with 8+ Yrs of exp looking for SDET Lead/SDET/ Scrum Master/Program Manager roles.", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Ganesh AlalaSundaram", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Ganesh AlalaSundaram"}, {"ExperianceYears": "8+ Yrs", "start_idx": 50, "tag": "ExperianceYears", "text": "8+ Yrs"}]}
{"line": "Willing to relocate: Anywhere WORK EXPERIENCE Consultant SDET Microsoft - June 2013 to Present", "tags": [{"Designation": "Consultant", "start_idx": 482, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Consultant"}, {"ORG": "SDET Microsoft", "start_idx": 493, "tag": "ORG", "text": "SDET Microsoft"}, {"DATE": "June 2013", "start_idx": 510, "tag": "DATE", "text": "June 2013"}, {"DATE": "Present", "start_idx": 523, "tag": "DATE", "text": "Present"}]}
{"line": "process. Programmer Analyst Cognizant - March 2010 to May 2013 Built WCF services for iOS and Android Applications for a PoC which helped business to grab more mobile projects. Delivered quality of products to customers with the stipulated time. Stand-ups, defect triage, brown bag sessions, bug-bash and retrospectives. Owned and managed weekly quality", "tags": [{"Designation": "Programmer Analyst", "start_idx": 792, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Programmer Analyst"}, {"ORG": "Cognizant", "start_idx": 811, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Cognizant"}, {"DATE": "March 2010", "start_idx": 823, "tag": "DATE", "text": "March 2010"}, {"DATE": "May 2013", "start_idx": 837, "tag": "DATE", "text": "May 2013"}]}
{"line": "report. Initiated transformation of web to mobile apps within project and assisted senior stakeholders of the company in analyzing the opportunity.", "tags": []}
{"line": "Projects IoT and Smart City Projects Formulated the use of VSO Dashboards for ease of status reporting which reduced manual effort of an hour per day.", "tags": []}
{"line": "https://www.indeed.com/r/Ganesh-AlalaSundaram/dd5b500021e61f65 isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN https://www.indeed.com/r/Ganesh-AlalaSundaram/dd5b500021e61f65 isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN Leveraged developer background to automate UI and API components through C#, Xamarin UI in iOS and Android apps. Led process improvements that standardized operations that included on-boarding/reporting and customer acceptance.", "tags": []}
{"line": "PubSec Projects - Dubai/Columbia/New York Coordinated between in-house and client teams and kept stakeholders informed of progress and milestones. Supervised an avg. of 10-member software QA team in developing and implementing quality- assurance and quality-control methodologies to ensure compliance with QA standards. Created tools that helped the development ecosystem by automating the long running", "tags": []}
{"line": "manual process. Brought a strong focus on \"voice of the customer\" into the software development function to ensure product and customer success Portfolio MSDN Blog - https://blogs.msdn.microsoft.com/ganesh/ GitHub Repo- https://github.com/ganesh-alalasundaram/ Personal Website: http://www.ganeshalalasundaram.com", "tags": []}
{"line": "EDUCATION Software Product Management Product School - New York, NY Bachelor of Computer Science in Computer Science Engineering", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "Bachelor of Computer Science in Computer Science Engineering", "start_idx": 2657, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "Bachelor of Computer Science in Computer Science Engineering"}]}
{"line": "Anna University SKILLS Automation, Testing, Mobile Testing, SDET, Scrum Master CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES", "tags": [{"ORG": "Anna University", "start_idx": 0, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Anna University"}, {"Skills": "Automation, Testing, Mobile Testing, SDET, Scrum Master", "start_idx": 23, "tag": "Skills", "text": "Automation, Testing, Mobile Testing, SDET, Scrum Master"}]}
{"line": "Certified ScrumMaster (CSM) PUBLICATIONS MSDN https://blogs.msdn.microsoft.com/ganesh GIT https://github.com/ganesh-alalasundaram https://blogs.msdn.microsoft.com/ganesh", "tags": []}
{"line": "CURRICULUM VITAE PERSONAL INFORMATION NAME- Garvit Shankar lohani ADDRERSS- 116 Vikas kunj Vikas Puri New Delhi 110018", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Garvit Shankar lohani", "start_idx": 317, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Garvit Shankar lohani"}, {"GPE": "New Delhi", "start_idx": 375, "tag": "GPE", "text": "New Delhi"}]}
{"line": "PHONE NUMBER- 9958629443 DATE OF BIRTH- 27/08/1996 PREFERRED LANGUAGE- HINDI&ENGLISH EDUCATION QUALIFICATION", "tags": [{"Phone": "9958629443", "start_idx": 406, "tag": "Phone", "text": "9958629443"}, {"DOB": "27/08/1996", "start_idx": 432, "tag": "DOB", "text": "27/08/1996"}, {"LANGUAGE": "HINDI&ENGLISH", "start_idx": 463, "tag": "LANGUAGE", "text": "HINDI&ENGLISH"}]}
{"line": "10Th - Holy Innocent Public School Vikas Puri ( 4% 2012", "tags": [{"CARDINAL": "4%", "start_idx": 549, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "4%"}]}
{"line": "12th - Holy Innocent Public School Vikas Puri ( 1% 2014", "tags": [{"CARDINAL": "1%", "start_idx": 605, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "1%"}, {"DATE": "2014", "start_idx": 608, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2014"}]}
{"line": "Graduation- BA (PROGRAME) Shivaji College Raja Garden University Of Delhi ( 0% 2018", "tags": [{"EducationDegree": "BA (PROGRAME)", "start_idx": 12, "tag": "EducationDegree", "text": "BA (PROGRAME)"}, {"ORG": "Shivaji College Raja Garden University Of Delhi", "start_idx": 26, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Shivaji College Raja Garden University Of Delhi"}, {"CARDINAL": "0%", "start_idx": 76, "tag": "CARDINAL", "text": "0%"}, {"DATE": "2018", "start_idx": 79, "tag": "DATE", "text": "2018"}]}
{"line": "Experience ORGANIZATION- CONCENTRIX EXPERIENCE- 12/03/2018- CURRENTLY WORKING POSITION- ADMIN (YT OPERATIONS)", "tags": [{"ORG": "CONCENTRIX", "start_idx": 25, "tag": "ORG", "text": "CONCENTRIX"}, {"DATE": "12/03/2018- CURRENTLY", "start_idx": 48, "tag": "DATE", "text": "12/03/2018- CURRENTLY"}, {"Designation": "ADMIN", "start_idx": 88, "tag": "Designation", "text": "ADMIN"}, {"ORG": "(YT OPERATIONS)", "start_idx": 94, "tag": "ORG", "text": "(YT OPERATIONS)"}]}
{"line": "KEY ROLES Reviewing and filtering YouTube content according to given policies", "tags": []}
{"line": "Account Monetization/Demonetization Taking action on YouTube comments according to policy guidelines", "tags": []}
{"line": "CARRER OBJECTIVE Looking for an organization who can analyze my true potential. And sharp my skill giving me an edge over this", "tags": []}
{"line": "Puneeth R Escalation Specialist - HiPower Support Centre Bengaluru, Karnataka - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Puneeth-R/bc332220e733906d", "tags": [{"PERSON": "Puneeth R", "start_idx": 306, "tag": "PERSON", "text": "Puneeth R"}, {"Designation": "Escalation Specialist", "start_idx": 316, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Escalation Specialist"}, {"GPE": "Bengaluru, Karnataka", "start_idx": 363, "tag": "GPE", "text": "Bengaluru, Karnataka"}]}
{"line": "To be an asset to my organization by utilizing the recent improving trends and make optimum use of the available resources for the success of the company. More importantly, working harmoniously in a team to bring forth the best from self and everyone.", "tags": []}
{"line": "June 2015 to Present Client: Machine Zone (Supporting 3 Games) Roles &amp; Responsibilities: Escalating tickets to clients, Creating Inquiries regarding the process to receive update from Clients, Providing feedback to Agents regarding Clients Escalations and internal invalid Escalations. Team handling ( Mentor) Tracking performances of the team members in terms of Production, Quality and", "tags": [{"DATE": "June 2015", "start_idx": 791, "tag": "DATE", "text": "June 2015"}, {"DATE": "Present", "start_idx": 804, "tag": "DATE", "text": "Present"}]}
{"line": "CSAT. Monitoring Queue, Allocating Agents to different queues, Preparing Reports, Process improvements initiatives. Taking operations training sessions on Gameplay, DSAT reviews, Quality, FTR and Tickets handling. Maintaining &amp; ensuring stringent adherence to quality standards, identifying gaps and opportunities by live assistance. Handled OJT and Tenured Team. Handling Supervisor tickets, Lead compensations and", "tags": []}
{"line": "Audits. Sales Associate in Convergys AT&T - January 2014 to May 2015", "tags": [{"Designation": "Sales Associate", "start_idx": 1611, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Sales Associate"}, {"ORG": "Convergys AT&T", "start_idx": 1630, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Convergys AT&T"}, {"DATE": "January 2014", "start_idx": 1647, "tag": "DATE", "text": "January 2014"}, {"DATE": "May 2015", "start_idx": 1663, "tag": "DATE", "text": "May 2015"}]}
{"line": "Process Executive - Operations in Infosys Cisco - August 2012 to November 2013", "tags": [{"Designation": "Process Executive", "start_idx": 166, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Process Executive"}, {"ORG": "Operations in Infosys Cisco", "start_idx": 186, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Operations in Infosys Cisco"}, {"DATE": "August 2012 to November 2013", "start_idx": 216, "tag": "DATE", "text": "August 2012 to November 2013"}]}
{"line": "Client: Cisco https://www.indeed.com/r/Puneeth-R/bc332220e733906d isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN Contd., Roles &amp; Responsibilities: Assisting Clients over Email and Phone regarding Billing discrepancies and Order Management. CRM tool experience in Supporting and Reports generation.", "tags": [{"ORG": "Cisco", "start_idx": 8, "tag": "ORG", "text": "Cisco"}]}
{"line": "Customer Relations Officer in HGS - December 2011 to July 2012", "tags": [{"Designation": "Customer Relations Officer", "start_idx": 296, "tag": "Designation", "text": "Customer Relations Officer"}, {"ORG": "HGS", "start_idx": 326, "tag": "ORG", "text": "HGS"}, {"DATE": "December 2011 to July 2012", "start_idx": 332, "tag": "DATE", "text": "December 2011 to July 2012"}]}
{"line": "Client: MTS Making calls to customers to review customer satisfaction and upselling. Handled Escalations from Customers. Taking Calls to address Customers Inquiries.", "tags": []}
